<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Ankit.Digital</title>
    <link href="https://ankit.digital/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://ankit.digital" />
    <updated>1970-01-01T05:30:00+05:30</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://ankit.digital</id>

    <entry>
        <title>LeadPages Vs ClickFunnels: The Ultimate Review</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankit.digital/leadpages-vs-clickfunnels.html"/>
        <id>https://ankit.digital/leadpages-vs-clickfunnels.html</id>
            <category term="Reviews"/>
            <category term="LeadPages"/>
            <category term="Comparison of LeadPages vs ClickFunnels"/>
            <category term="ClickFunnels Reveiw"/>

        <updated>2020-10-07T02:08:34+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/LeadPages-Vs-ClickFunnels.png" alt="LeadPages Vs ClickFunnels" />
                    Are you looking for a review of Leadpages vs ClickFunnels? Not sure&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/LeadPages-Vs-ClickFunnels.png" alt="LeadPages Vs ClickFunnels" />
                <p>Are you looking for a review of <a href="https://ankit.digital/leadpages-review.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Leadpages</a> vs <a href="https://ankit.digital/clickfunnels-review.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">ClickFunnels</a>? Not sure whether to choose <strong>ClickFunnels or Leadpages</strong>?</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/leadpages-vs-clickfunnels.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/leadpages-vs-clickfunnels-xs.jpg 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/leadpages-vs-clickfunnels-sm.jpg 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/leadpages-vs-clickfunnels-md.jpg 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/leadpages-vs-clickfunnels-lg.jpg 1024w"  alt="LeadPages Vs ClickFunnels"></figure>
<p>Above are very hard questions but now you have come to the right place. In this review, we are taking a depth look at both of these marketing tools to help you which one is right for yours. In the world of marketing, there is no such thing as a “one size fits for all” tool. You can come into this review learning towards one but then you realize that the other one fits better.</p>
<p>We will look at both tools individually and then compare them together in a head to head match.</p>
<p>But before we discuss the tools let me explain the difference between a landing page and a funnel.</p>
<h2><strong>What is a Landing Page?</strong></h2>
<p>A landing page can be a page of your website that a new visitor lands first on that page. By definition, if we go then a landing page can be an email opt-in page, a sales page, your website’s homepage, a blog post, a product listing, or any other page on which you want to drive traffic.</p>
<p>In marketing, your goal is to create optimized landing pages for first-time visitors on your welcome page and help them to learn about your product or services. You may not make sales but you can collect email subscribers by offering lead forms or free ebooks or an email course.</p>
<h2><strong>What is Funnel?</strong></h2>
<p>The goal of your funnel may not be purchasing a product but it may be subscribing to your mailing list or signing up for a free trial. The ultimate goal is to make a sale but that is not mean that every funnel has to lead a sell.</p>
<p>You may also have several types of funnels on your site like:</p>
<ol>
<li>One that nurtures leads.</li>
<li>One that upsells your customers.</li>
<li>One that converts leads into your customers.</li>
</ol>
<p>Sales funnels are just a series of conversion-optimized pages.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/what-is-funnels.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/what-is-funnels-xs.jpg 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/what-is-funnels-sm.jpg 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/what-is-funnels-md.jpg 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/what-is-funnels-lg.jpg 1024w"  alt="what is funnels" width="723" height="427"></figure>
<h2><strong>What is ClickFunnels?</strong></h2>
<p>ClickFunnels is a marketing software that can help you to create conversion-optimized pages to use in your sales funnels. ClickFunnels was developed by Russell Brunson who was an Internet marketer, the best selling author, and also the founder of DotCom Secrets.</p>
<h3><strong>How does it work?</strong></h3>
<p>ClickFunnels allows you to create sales funnels and landing pages both. You can also run an email marketing service, track and also manage affiliates and even you can operate a membership website with ClickFunnels.</p>
<p>For using ClickFunnels you don’t need to be a web designer or developer to create web pages. With its share funnels feature, you don’t even need to be a good marketer to create a successful sales funnel.</p>
<p>For details of every feature offered by <span style="color: #236fa1;"><strong>ClickFunnels</strong></span>, you can read from our previous article.</p>
<p>Below are the features which make ClickFunnels such an outstanding marketing service.</p>
<p><strong>Create Sales Funnels</strong></p>
<p>Create a funnel for your goal using ClickFunnels. To do this you can select funnels from a library of pre-built funnels or create your own funnel from scratch.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/Create-Sales-Funnels.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/Create-Sales-Funnels-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/Create-Sales-Funnels-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/Create-Sales-Funnels-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/Create-Sales-Funnels-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Create a sales Funnel"></figure>
<p><strong>Create a Landing Page</strong></p>
<p>You can use this as a page editor to create your entire website if you would like. ClickFunnels can let you create landing pages up to 100 with the standard plan and up to 300 with the Elite plan.</p>
<p><strong>Host your landing pages on ClickFunnels</strong></p>
<p>You can host your landing pages on ClickFunnels without any issue with any plan you subscribed to.</p>
<p><strong>Get a custom domain</strong></p>
<p>You can register a new domain from ClickFunnel at an affordable cost.</p>
<p><strong>Use ClickFunnels with WordPress</strong></p>
<p>You can use ClickFunnels with WordPress by using ClickFunnels WordPress plugin with which you can easily integrate.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/Create-a-Landing-Page.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/Create-a-Landing-Page-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/Create-a-Landing-Page-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/Create-a-Landing-Page-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/Create-a-Landing-Page-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Create a landing page with ClickFunnels"></figure>
<p><strong>Share your funnels with others</strong></p>
<p>You can share your funnels with others also with ClickFunnels sharing feature.</p>
<p><strong>Nurture leads with the built-in email autoresponder</strong></p>
<p>You can nurture your leads with the built-in email autoresponder without going to another email marketing tool software or service.</p>
<p><strong>Perform split testing</strong></p>
<p>With ClickFunnels, you can do split testing of various versions of your landing pages after creating variations of your landing pages with some changes.</p>
<h3><strong>ClickFunnels Integrations</strong></h3>
<p>Here is the list of all the integrations provided by ClickFunnels:</p>
<p><strong>Email Integrations:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>ActiveCampaign</li>
<li>AWeber</li>
<li>Constant Contact</li>
<li>ConvertKit</li>
<li>Drip</li>
<li>GetResponse</li>
<li>GVO Pure Leverage</li>
<li>HTML Form Integrations</li>
<li>HubSpot</li>
<li>Infusionsoft</li>
<li>Madmimi</li>
<li>MailChimp</li>
<li>Maropost</li>
<li>Ontraport</li>
<li>Salesforce</li>
<li>Sendlane</li>
<li>ZenPlanner</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Payment Gateway Integrations:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Braintree</li>
<li>ClickBank</li>
<li>Deal Guardian</li>
<li>EasyPayDirect</li>
<li>InfusionSoft</li>
<li>JV Zoo</li>
<li>NMI</li>
<li>Ontraport</li>
<li>PayPal</li>
<li>Recurly</li>
<li>Stripe</li>
<li>Taxamo</li>
<li>Warrior Plus</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>ClickFunnels Support &amp; Community</strong></h3>
<p>For supporting customers, ClickFunnels had done their job well. After signing up, you can start with six pre-built funnels.</p>
<p>And if you need any help, you can find a ton of resources in the help center. In the help center, you can find topics related to start creating with ClickFunnels to integrating third-party tools, everything in detail how you can do a start and creating funnels for your marketing.</p>
<p>And if you can’t find your answer in the help center articles then you can simply click the live chat to send a message to the support team and someone will get back to you within an hour. Also, you can reach ClickFunnels over Facebook also.</p>
<h3><strong>Pricing offered by ClickFunnels</strong></h3>
<p>The base plan starts with $97 per month in which you will get 14 days free trial to test all the features, and if you will pay for one year in advance you will get a free two-month subscription.</p>
<p>The second plan, known as Etison Elite, which is the full suite of services offered by ClickFunnels.</p>
<h2><strong>What is Leadpages?</strong></h2>
<p>Leadpages is a landing page builder with various marketing features for marketers. You can use this tool to create an optimized sales page from where you can collect and manage contacts for your marketing efforts.</p>
<p>Leadpages is more than just a landing page builder. With leadpages, you can use Leadboxes to create pop-up opt-in forms that can be placed on any page of your website. You can also generate leads via email with Leadlinks. Finally, Leaddigits allows you to get subscribers or contacts via text message also.</p>
<h3><strong>How does it work?</strong></h3>
<p>Leadpages is perfect for beginners who are just looking for a simple tool that is also budget-friendly. With the use of Leadpages, you will get a very intuitive experience. Even if you have never created landing pages before you will also feel confident using Leadpages on your first try.</p>
<p>Also, Leadpages works with all the major email service providers, so you can collect emails and continue to collect leads who have signed up through your landing page.</p>
<p>For details of every feature offered by <strong>Leadpages</strong>, you can read from our previous article.</p>
<p>With Leadpages you can create landing pages to offer products or services to your visitors who come first on a web page to deliver automatic digital assets with Leadpages.</p>
<p>Below are the features which make Leadpages such an outstanding landing page builder and marketing software.</p>
<p><strong>Drag and Drop Customization</strong></p>
<p>With Drag and drop customization in Leadpages, you can easily build your landing page from the pre-built template as well as from scratch. It is quite easier than doing with self or manual customization.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/Drag-and-Drop-Customization.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/Drag-and-Drop-Customization-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/Drag-and-Drop-Customization-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/Drag-and-Drop-Customization-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/36/responsive/Drag-and-Drop-Customization-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Drag and Drop Customization with LeadPages" width="719" height="397"></figure>
<p><strong>Pre-Built Landing pages</strong></p>
<p>Leadpages also provides a number of pre-built landing page templates you just need to select the template you want to use and start the drag and drop customization in a very easy manner.</p>
<p><strong>Split testing for your landing pages</strong></p>
<p>With Leadpages you can do split testing for your landing pages and what you want to test about how much traffic you will get on that particular variant of the landing page.</p>
<p><strong>Lead Notifications</strong></p>
<p>If you have created a landing page but you have not connected any email marketing software then you don’t need to worry about your leads. You will get notified via your registered email id for your upcoming leads from your particular landing pages.</p>
<p>This is a great feature Leadpages comes with.</p>
<p><strong>SMS Sign-ups</strong></p>
<p>No one wants to see a lot of sign up forms for your lists. You should make it easy on them. Leadpages gives you the option to offer SMS sign up. With Leadpages you can send a text to their phone, they can respond to you with an email address. You will get this feature with LeadDigits which is one of the special features or addon by Leadpages.</p>
<p><strong>Easy to use opt-in Pop-ups</strong></p>
<p>As we all know about Pop-ups which are the proven method to capture leads. Use Leadboxes to create various types of opt-ins including your favorite pop-up or the exit intent. You can also use their WordPress plugin and embed these pop-ups on your blog posts outside the LeadPages.</p>
<p><strong>LeadDigits</strong></p>
<p>LeadDigits allows you to collect email leads through text message instead of asking people to visit on your website, just you need to ask them to text your LeadDigits number. Once they provide you their contact number they will get an automated text asking them to sign up to your email list. LeadDigits also offers an experience that will also improve your conversion rates. Because people will forget to look at your website.</p>
<h3><strong>Leadpages Integrations</strong></h3>
<p>Here is the list of all the integrations provided by Leadpages:</p>
<h4><strong>Email Integrations Supported by Leadpages</strong></h4>
<ul>
<li>1ShoppingCart</li>
<li>ActiveCampaign</li>
<li>AWeber</li>
<li>ConstantContact</li>
<li>Drip</li>
<li>Emma</li>
<li>GetResponse</li>
<li>GoToWebinar</li>
<li>Hubspot</li>
<li>iContact</li>
<li>InfusionSoft</li>
<li>Interspire</li>
<li>MadMimi</li>
<li>Marketo</li>
<li>MailChimp</li>
<li>OfficeAutoPilot</li>
<li>Salesforce</li>
<li>SendReach</li>
<li>WebinarJam</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>Leadpages Support &amp; Community</strong></h3>
<p>Leadpages run various training webinars frequently with the aim of helping you to get more. Also, you can get more help from their active blogs, collection of marketing resources, and knowledge base. But they can’t provide chat on their site, chat feature is only available inside the Leadpage app for Pro and advanced members.</p>
<h3><strong>Pricing offered by Leadpages</strong></h3>
<p>Leadpages offered three-tiered pricing plans which are Standard, Pro, and advanced.</p>
<p>Also, you can choose a month to month billing for standard and Pro plan. The advanced plan requires an annual or two-year payment upfront. You will save quite a bit more if you will pay for annual and especially for a two-year service in which pricing is cut off in half as compared to monthly billing.</p>
<p><strong>Standard Plan</strong></p>
<p>In this plan, you have to pay $17 per month when you purchase two years upfront, $25 per month when you will purchase annually, and $37 for a month to month plan. Month to month is still in your budget if you will get such great features inside in comparison with ClickFunnels.</p>
<p><strong>Pro Plan</strong></p>
<p>In this plan, you need to pay $42 per month when you purchase for two years, $48 per month when you will purchase annually and $79 for a month to month plan.</p>
<p><strong>Advanced Plan</strong></p>
<p>This plan does not offer month to month plan. For annual billing you need to pay $199 per month and for two year purchase, you need to pay $159 per month.</p>
<h3><strong>ClickFunnels Vs. Leadpages</strong></h3>
<p>There a various factors that I personally believe most people will look at price and ease of use.</p>
<p>When you will see for price compatibility then Leadpages is the winner here. It is a bit cheaper than ClickFunnels.</p>
<p>There is a reason why Leadpages is much cheaper than ClickFunnels like Leadpages are not that much convenient than ClickFunnels.</p>
<p>You don’t need a separate web host or a seperate email marketing or shopping cart solution. Also you don’t need a seperate affiliate program. Everything is included in just one package.</p>
<p>If you are looking at this way then ClickFunnels is very budget friendly in its own right. But, I do think Leadpages is an awesome choice in some situations. If you want to create landing pages much quickly without more customization then Leadpages is a greap platform for you.</p>
<p>So, which should you choose?</p>
<p>Go with <span style="color: #236fa1;">Leadpages</span> if you want a budget marketing software that can get the job done. You can create beautiful sales pages without knowing a bit of codes.</p>
<p>Go with <span style="color: #236fa1;">ClickFunnels</span> if you want to create an effective conversion optimized funnel pages without learning HTML.</p>
<p>Go with <span style="color: #236fa1;">Leadpages</span> if you simply want to design landing pages with a simple one-step landing page.</p>
<p>Go with <span style="color: #236fa1;">ClickFunnels</span> if you don’t want to use different systems for marketing program. You will save much time with an all in one solution.</p>
<p>Go with <span style="color: #236fa1;">ClickFunnels</span>, if you want to create an funnel with multiple pages along with the flexibility to rearrange the pages in your funnel.</p>
<h6>Conclusion</h6>
<p>I love to use both ClickFunnels and Leadpages, and I think both are great tools for converting leads. You can only build pages on Leadpages but you can build pages and build funnels as well on ClickFunnels. The right choice for you will mainly depend on what you need from a marketing tool. But if you are still not confirmed about which one to use then you should try 14 days free trial of ClickFunnels and test all features. If you find that is not good for your business then cancel and check out Leadpages. I am about 90% sure that ClickFunnels will do everything you want.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Thrive Architect Vs LeadPages: The Ultimate Review</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankit.digital/thrive-architect-vs-leadpages.html"/>
        <id>https://ankit.digital/thrive-architect-vs-leadpages.html</id>
            <category term="Thrive Themes"/>
            <category term="Thrive Architect Vs LeadPages"/>
            <category term="Thrive Architect Reviews"/>
            <category term="Review"/>
            <category term="LeadPages"/>
            <category term="Landing Page"/>

        <updated>2020-10-07T02:08:34+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/35/Thrive-Vs-Leadpages.png" alt="" />
                    LeadPages and Thrive Architect both are landing page builders. Basically both are&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/35/Thrive-Vs-Leadpages.png" alt="" />
                <p><span style="color: #000000;">LeadPages and Thrive Architect both are landing page builders. Basically both are very helpful in lead capturing like name, emails, and phone number, and the details you want from your visitors. And also both can be useful in selling a digital course or any product. Today in this post I will show you similarities and differences between LeadPages and Thrive Architect (Product of <a href="https://ankit.digital/thrive-themes-review.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" style="color: #000000;">Thrive Themes</a>) and in the end, you can use any tool you want after reading this complete post.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>What Is LeadPages?</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">In terms of page customization, LeadPages has two types of templates which are Standard and Drag-and-drop, builders.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">However, Leadpages is a hosted solution that means you can host your landing pages on the Leadpages server, your own server, or even on Facebook too.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">For detailed information on LeadPages, you can read our deep review on <strong><a href="https://ankit.digital/leadpages-review.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" style="color: #000000;">LeadPages Review</a>.</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Some Key features of LeadPages are:</strong></span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Template Library</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Responsive</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Affiliate Program</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Welcome Gate (or Equivalent)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Exit Intent Pop-ups</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Marketing Tool Integrations</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">LeadBox (or Equivalent)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">SEO Optimized</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Customer Support</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">30 Day Money Back Guarantee</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">LeadLinks (or Equivalent)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Build From Scratch Drag &amp; Drop</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Facebook Integration</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">No Website Required</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Sort Landing Pages by Conversion Rate</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">LeadDigits (or Equivalent)</span></li>
</ol>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>What is Thrive Architect (Thrive Themes)?</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">In terms of Page customization, you can change everything about every template, and also you can add any of the 37 elements which include texts, buttons, boxes, and testimonials, etc. anywhere on any page, you want to add.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">However, the Thrive Suite is a pack of WordPress plugins which means you can only use this on a self-hosted site which is running on WordPress.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">For detailed information on Thrive Themes, you can read our deep review on <a href="https://ankit.digital/thrive-themes-review.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" style="color: #000000;">Thrive Themes</a>.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Some Key features of Thrive Themes are:</strong></span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">All features of Leadpages.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Own Your Pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">SmartLinks (or Equivalent)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">TypeFocus (or Equivalent)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Search Engine Optimized Blog Creation</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Content Marketing Reporting Tools</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Opt-In Form Targeting &amp; Segmentation</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Fully Integrated Websites (w/ navigation)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Evergreen &amp; Uncheatable Countdown Timers</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Automatic Headline Optimization</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Testimonial Organization &amp; Management</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Landing Page A/B Testing</span></li>
</ol>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Key Differences between Leadpages and Thrive Architect</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">In Thrive Themes, Thrive Architect is the product from which you can build beautiful Landing pages even you can build your custom theme or website also very easily.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Thrive Architect and LeadPages both are very different products. And they do many of the same things but at their core, they are very different.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><em>“The biggest difference between <strong>LeadPages</strong> and Thrive Architect is LeadPages is a Hosted Solution and <strong>Thrive Architect</strong> is a WordPress Plugin.”</em></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">It means:</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">You can use leadpages without having a website and on the other hand, thrive architect will work only on WordPress websites that are self-hosted by you.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">You can't thrive architect if you don’t have a WordPress website. And in this case, LeadPages is a better solution for you.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">So why we are comparing both products, see below:</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">If you have a website running on WordPress you can use Thrive Architect and Leadpages both which makes things interesting if you are trying to decide between these two.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">See how we have organized the comparison of both:</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Let's compare the standard level of LeadPages with Thrive Architect first.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Comparison of LeadPages (Standard Plan) and Thrive Architect</strong></span></h3>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Pricing of Standard Level of LeadPages and Thrive Architect:</strong></span></h4>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Thrive Architect Pricing:</strong></span></h5>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">15 License Pack- $147</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">5 License Pack- $97</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">1 License Pack- $67</span></li>
</ul>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>What you will get</strong>:</span></h5>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Full Feature Set​</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Activate on 1, 5, or 15 sites</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited Updates</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">1 Year of Unlimited Support</span></li>
</ul>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>LeadPages Standard Plan Pricing:</strong></span></h5>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">$300/Year</span></li>
</ul>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>What you will get:</strong></span></h5>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited Landing Pages/Unlimited Domains</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">All Page Templates &amp; Leadboxes</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Embed on Any Site</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Advanced HTML Export</span></li>
</ul>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Features of Standard Level of LeadPages and Thrive Architect:</strong></span></h4>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Features of LeadPages (Standard Plan)</strong></span></h5>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Template Library</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Responsive</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Welcome Gate (or Equivalent)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Exit Intent Pop-ups</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Marketing Tool Integrations</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">LeadBox (or Equivalent)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">SEO Optimized</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Customer Support</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">30 Day Money Back Guarantee</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Build From Scratch Drag &amp; Drop</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Facebook Integration</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">No Website Required</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Sort Landing Pages by Conversion Rate</span></li>
</ul>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Features of Thrive Architect</strong></span></h5>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Template Library</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Responsive</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Affiliate Program</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Exit Intent Pop-ups</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Marketing Tool Integrations</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">LeadBox (or Equivalent)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">SEO Optimized</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Customer Support</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">30 Day Money Back Guarantee</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Own Your Pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Build From Scratch Drag &amp; Drop</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">No Monthly Fees</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">There is a major difference between these two products which are price and core functionality such as WordPress plugin vs hosted solution.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">These above products are entry-level products for both companies and as a beginner, a larger factor is the price and especially if there is another product that has similar features. If your budget is low and you want such features to build and promote online business then Thrive Architect is a better choice for you.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">And if you want to build more than just landing pages for your online business then you will get better options and helpful solutions in the below section.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Comparison of Thrive Membership and LeadPages (Pro Level)</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Thrive Membership and LeadPages Pro is a very interesting and helpful comparison if you want to grow your online business for the long term. These products are focused to generate more leads for your business in more aspects than just landing pages and both have more features to compare.</span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Pricing Comparison</strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Pricing of Thrive Membership</strong></span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--left"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/35/thrive-themes.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/35/responsive/thrive-themes-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/35/responsive/thrive-themes-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/35/responsive/thrive-themes-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/35/responsive/thrive-themes-lg.png 1024w"  alt="thrive themes" width="235" height="71"></figure></span></p>
<p> </p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Personal License (Use on 25 Websites)- $228/Year</span></li>
</ul>
<h6><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>What you will get in this pack:</strong></span></h6>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">You will get complete access to Thrive Suite which includes Thrive Architect, Thrive Leads, all Thrive Themes for WordPress, Thrive Headline Optimizer, Thrive Ultimatum, Thrive Quiz Builder, Thrive Comments, Thrive Ovation and Thrive Optimize, and more.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">All upcoming plugins, themes, updates, and features.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited Access to Support.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Pricing of LeadPages Pro</strong></span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--left"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/35/Leadpages-pro.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/35/responsive/Leadpages-pro-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/35/responsive/Leadpages-pro-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/35/responsive/Leadpages-pro-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/35/responsive/Leadpages-pro-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Leadpages Pro"></figure></span></p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Everything in Standard Plan and more- $576/Year</span></li>
</ul>
<h6><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>What you will get in this pack:</strong></span></h6>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">A/B Testing &amp; LeadDigits</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Access to Affiliate Program &amp; Discounts for Partners</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Upload Custom Landing Page Templates</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Priority Email Support &amp; Live Chat</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Every future plugin, theme, update, and feature.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited access to support</span></li>
</ul>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Features Comparison of LeadPages Pro and Thrive Membership</strong></span></h3>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Features in LeadPages Pro:</strong></span></h4>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Template Library</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Responsive</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Affiliate Program</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Welcome Gate (or Equivalent)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Exit Intent Pop-ups</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Marketing Tool Integrations</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">LeadBox (or Equivalent)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">SEO Optimized</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Customer Support</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">30 Day Money Back Guarantee</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">LeadLinks (or Equivalent)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Build From Scratch Drag &amp; Drop</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Landing Page A/B Testing</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Facebook Integration</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">No Website Required</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Sort Landing Pages by Conversion Rate</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">LeadDigits (or Equivalent)</span></li>
</ul>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Features in Thrive Membership:</strong></span></h4>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Template Library</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Responsive</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Affiliate Program</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Welcome Gate (or Equivalent)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Exit Intent Pop-ups</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Marketing Tool Integrations</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">LeadBox (or Equivalent)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">SEO Optimized</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Customer Support</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">30 Day Money Back Guarantee</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">LeadLinks (or Equivalent)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Build From Scratch Drag &amp; Drop</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Own Your Pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">SmartLinks (or Equivalent)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">TypeFocus (or Equivalent)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Search Engine Optimized Blog Creation</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Content Marketing Reporting Tools</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Opt-In Form Targeting &amp; Segmentation</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Fully Integrated Websites (w/ navigation)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Evergreen &amp; Uncheatable Countdown Timers</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Automatic Headline Optimization</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Testimonial Organization &amp; Management</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Landing Page A/B Testing</span></li>
</ul>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Ease of Use Comparison of LeadPages Pro Vs Thrive Membership</strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">All visual editors are much the same but this is where the smallest details or points in terms of usability becomes important. While you are building complex pages and websites which involve hundreds of user actions. If an editor is a few seconds slower on any step, then it can turn to frustrating hours.</span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Thrive Membership Ease of Use</strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">If you are new to WordPress then you have various things to learn and build your online business and generate more leads.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">When you will get to know everything about drag and drop editor, then it’s not just simple and fast to use but very powerful also and takes you to feel of designer level customization.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Thrive has a huge knowledge base of training content and also there are new features you can expect blog posts and various learning videos to explain its features and how to use them in a very easier manner.</span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>LeadPages Pro Ease of Use</strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Standard templates or LeadPages Pro are designed for quick development only allows you to swap some key elements for your industry before publishing.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Hence, once you are ready to use it then you can use it with just some clicks on what you want to edit and then edit it.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Also, their drag-and-drop editor also much more useful than the standard template editor but is not very flexible means you can drag-and-drop elements on the landing page but when you want to move page sections requires drag-and-dropping from the sidebar menu then you need their draggable columns to create width layouts.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">However, LeadPages also has an extensive knowledge base, and also you can choose from some great tutorials and webinars which teach you how to use their features and take advantage of the product.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>User Support Comparison of LeadPages Pro and Thrive Membership</strong></span></h3>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>User Support in Thrive Membership</strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">If you have purchased Thrive Membership then you will also get unlimited access to their support team till that time when you are a member. If you will purchase a single <strong>Thrive Product</strong> then you will get access to one year of unlimited support and if you will need help after that one year then you can also extend your support term with a small fee.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">The support team is very fast and <strong>extremely knowledgeable</strong>. Just you need to do is log in to the support forum and post a ticket and you will get a response on the same day.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">As my personal experience, there is a rare case they can’t solve your issue through the ticket then they can log in to your website if you want and fix it for you with security.</span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>User Support in LeadPages Pro</strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">When you have purchased a LeadPages membership, then your support level depends on your subscription plan. At the basic plan, you have access to the knowledge base, and also you can submit support tickets from your account dashboard.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">At the Pro Level you will get access to personal support chat which is available for you from Monday to Friday from 9 am to 5 pm and also you can able to submit support tickets.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">At the Expertise level, you can submit support tickets, use live chat, and also you can get live phone support which is available for Monday to Friday from 9 am to 5 pm CST.</span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Overall Comparision Of Both (LeadPages and Thrive Membership</strong></span></h4>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>LeadPages Pro</strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">LeadPages can be a great option for you if you don’t have a website based on WordPress CMS  because it allows you to host your landing pages on its own servers. However, this also means that you can’t own your pages so if you will cancel your subscription then all of your pages are lost.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">There are also some cool and amazing features like:</span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">LeadDigits</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Facebook Integration</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">LeadLinks</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">For the Complete Feature overview, you can get it from <strong><a href="https://ankit.digital/leadpages-review.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" style="color: #000000;">here</a></strong>.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>LeadPages Pro</strong> is just more than double the price of Thrive Membership ($588/Year vs $228/year), so if pricing is a concern for you then there is a large gap between the two, even they are capable of doing the same things.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Thrive Membership</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Thrive Membership can be an amazing solution for boosting the conversion of your website if your website is on WordPress and you can own your pages after your membership canceled also.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Thrive membership also gives you access to all of Thrive’s current and upcoming plugins and themes. Which includes the content builder from which you can do complete drag-and-drop customization with zero designing skills for any and all the pages you own, forms, and blog posts.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">When you will integrate with the Thrive leads plugin then you will get that functionality that can give you a better response than LeadPages with a few different features.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">This also includes reporting tools for content marketing so you can fully get reports on what works with your audience and brings in the most leads as well as options to automatically target and offers to different visitors segments.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">And also you can get its membership for just payment of $228/year which is much lesser than LeadPages. You can get access to every product created by Thrive, all upcoming updates, lifetime support, and if <strong>Thrive Price</strong> increased then you don’t need to pay extra in the membership period.</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Unbounce Review 2020 | Pros, Cons, Features</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankit.digital/unbounce-review.html"/>
        <id>https://ankit.digital/unbounce-review.html</id>
            <category term="Unbounce Review"/>
            <category term="Reviews"/>
            <category term="Landing Page"/>
            <category term="Digital Marketing"/>

        <updated>2020-10-07T02:08:34+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/Unbounce-Reviews.png" alt="" />
                    Introduction To UnbounceWith the help of Unbounce, you can create and design&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/Unbounce-Reviews.png" alt="" />
                <h2><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Introduction To Unbounce</strong></span></h2>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With the help of Unbounce, you can create and design beautiful Landing pages that will convert leads for you with their pre-built landing page templates, and more features are built it to make sure your website visitors converted into your customers.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">They have features like:</span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Build Any Page on Your Own</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Create the Exact Page You Want</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Continually Grow Your ROI</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Popups builder</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Landing page builder</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With Unbounce, you can create custom landing pages without a piece of coding knowledge. Also, you can get the highest converting campaigns possible with Unbounce Conversion intelligence and latest AI Feature and smart traffic.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">As we all know websites are great for information and exploration, Unbounce can turn your website’s traffic into revenue, how we will discuss here. With Unbounce, you can create and optimize your dedicated landing pages that focus your visitors on one goal instead of bouncing them back from the distractions.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With an easy drag and drop landing page and popup builder and also with the help of 100+ landing page templates, you can easily bring any of your campaign vision to life in just a fraction of the time it will take with a developer.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">And also design pages that look and act almost 100% the way you want to create. You can put any looks and functionality you want with the customizable templates with optional Javascripts and CSS for both mobile and desktop versions.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With Unbounce, get a built-in AI Conversion power with smart traffic and A/B Tester for your landing pages to see what’s exactly working. You can experiment with messaging, designs, and forms to validate what makes more visitors can convert.</span></p>
<h2><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Why did we start using Unbounce?</strong></span></h2>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">It all comes down to the time it takes to design and develop new pages. Basically, landing pages were useful when we need to promote new products and any services.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">You often need multiple landing pages at any one time and also for different products or websites, PPC campaigns, and email marketing campaigns.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With Unbounce, you can give your marketing team the power to create landing pages quickly and the key is Unbounce. It’s easy and quick.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Your first landing page design never gets the best results but practice and experiments do with A/B testings.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">To maximize the performance of your landing pages you need to optimize and test on an ongoing basis and this simply means you should create multiple variations for every landing page you build.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/unbounce-ab-testing.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/unbounce-ab-testing-xs.jpg 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/unbounce-ab-testing-sm.jpg 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/unbounce-ab-testing-md.jpg 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/unbounce-ab-testing-lg.jpg 1024w"  alt="unbounce ab testing" width="701" height="437"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">You should know that Unbounce comes with unlimited A/B Testing on all of its plans and you can use it for your landing pages built-in A/B Testing tool and you can do enough with the use of a single platform.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Also, Unbounce comes with a unique feature which is Dynamic Text replacement which can make personalization fast and easy to implement.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Unbounce is a conversion-driven platform</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">There are various types of landing page builders into the market but one of the things about Unbounce is that it is a purely <strong>conversion-driven platform</strong>. The whole point of creating landing pages is to convert the visitor into your customers or leads and paying customers.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">As I have already mentioned that Unbounce comes with unlimited A/B Testing which is a very useful tool for optimizing conversions with landing page variation experiments. But it also comes with Built-in tools designed only to capture more leads which includes popups, sticky bars, and AI Optimization features.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/Conversion-optimized-by-unbounce.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Conversion-optimized-by-unbounce-xs.jpg 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Conversion-optimized-by-unbounce-sm.jpg 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Conversion-optimized-by-unbounce-md.jpg 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Conversion-optimized-by-unbounce-lg.jpg 1024w"  alt="Conversion optimized by unbounce" width="714" height="649"></figure></span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Unbounce Pros &amp; Cons</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">In my point of view, Unbounce is a great software and there are various good things to say about it. There is always a need improvement in many cases as we have pointed all pros and cons we have experienced while using the platform.</span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Unbounce Pros</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">You can build and publish landing pages very quickly.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">You can easily create variants for testing.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Excellent templates and various third party sources for more templates.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Highly Customizable.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Awesome Landing page builder.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Split testing functions are very good.</span></li>
</ol>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Unbounce Cons</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Form builder of Unbounce lacks some key features.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">You can’t do a split test for your existing landing pages created outside of Unbounce.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">You can’t add custom classes to buttons in Unbounce which prevents tracking goals.</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">If Unbounce let you do split test the landing pages built outside the Unbounce then this would be a great win and the ability to add custom classes to buttons can save a lot of time as well.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">But overall, Unbounce can save you more time than it costs and once you are running with this platform then you can do things easily. The landing page builder is great and the templates available are excellent and you can also get the freedom to customize your landing pages.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Also, I must include the split testing feature which is solid and too sure that they are not extensive as a dedicated piece of <strong>A/B testing software</strong> but it is a strong offering for a landing page builder and also you can get more features than most of the alternatives.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Unbounce features: More than a landing page builder</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">As I have already explained above that Unbounce is a landing page builder primarily so the platform offers a set of features beyond its builder and many of these are very important when it comes to create and optimize landing pages like A/B Testing.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Here is the list of features offered by Unbounce:</span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Landing pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Popups &amp; sticky bars</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">A/B testing</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Reports &amp; analytics</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Dynamic Text Replacement</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Smart Traffic</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">AMP landing pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Lead form builder</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Let us explain every feature:</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Landing Pages Builder of UnBounce</strong>:</span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With <strong>Unbounce Drag and drop</strong>, landing page builder can make sure anyone anytime can pick up the tool and start creating pages without any coding knowledge or using any designing software.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/Landing-Pages-Builder-of-UnBounce.gif" alt="Landing Pages Builder of UnBounce" width="606" height="560"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">You can choose from a lot of templates to get started and customize them to meet your needs easily and quickly. Also to speed up the design process, you can clone and edit the entire pages, copy and paste them and save your own templates for next time.</span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Features of landing page builder are</strong>:</span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Drag-and-drop builder</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">100+ templates</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Clone &amp; edit</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Copy and paste</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Full control</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Quick publishing</span></li>
</ol>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Popups and Sticky Bars</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">After landing page builder, Unbounce also comes with its own <strong>sticky bar and popups builder</strong> which can be used for boosting conversions so there is no denying that they can increase your conversion rates when used effectively.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/Popups-and-Sticky-Bars-builder.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Popups-and-Sticky-Bars-builder-xs.jpg 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Popups-and-Sticky-Bars-builder-sm.jpg 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Popups-and-Sticky-Bars-builder-md.jpg 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Popups-and-Sticky-Bars-builder-lg.jpg 1024w"  alt=" Popups and Sticky Bars builder" width="713" height="648"></figure></span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Features of Popups and sticky bar builder are:</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Drag-and-drop builder</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Templates</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Targeting &amp; triggers</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Schedule</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">A/B testing</span></li>
</ol>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>A/B testing from Unbounce</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Unbounce provides various A/B Testing features on all of its plans which allows you to optimize your landing pages and popups for maximum performance.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">You can set up A/B Testing campaigns within some clicks to test entirely different pages, variations like the same page with or without a lead form or specific elements like call to action feature etc.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/AB-testing-from-Unbounce.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/AB-testing-from-Unbounce-xs.jpg 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/AB-testing-from-Unbounce-sm.jpg 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/AB-testing-from-Unbounce-md.jpg 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/AB-testing-from-Unbounce-lg.jpg 1024w"  alt="A/B testing from Unbounce" width="700" height="436"></figure></span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Report &amp; Analytics</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">This software provides insights into how your landing pages are performing and how your A/B Tests are going. You can access all of this in the dashboard but you will get the best results with the integration of Google Analytics.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/Report-and-analytics.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Report-and-analytics-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Report-and-analytics-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Report-and-analytics-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Report-and-analytics-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Report &amp; analytics" width="711" height="353"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">You can easily find the documentation on how to integrate Google Analytics with Unbounce but all you really need to do is get tracking id from Google Analytics to enter into Script Manager, which you can find under settings.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Dynamic Text Replacement</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">This feature helps in landing page personalisation. The feature matches the copy of the landing page based on the keywords typed by the users before clicking on your ads.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/Dynamic-Text-Replacement.gif" alt="Dynamic Text Replacement" width="573" height="436"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">To set up your dynamic text replacement in Unbounce, you can simply select the text you want to apply it to and then click the dynamic text button.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Smart Traffic</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Smart traffic is an AI based conversion tool that automatically looks at each visitor's attributes and directs them to the most relevant pages. The algorithm looks at attributes like user location and their device to determine which variations of landing pages will be more effective than others.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/Smart-Traffic-with-UnBounce.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Smart-Traffic-with-UnBounce-xs.jpg 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Smart-Traffic-with-UnBounce-sm.jpg 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Smart-Traffic-with-UnBounce-md.jpg 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Smart-Traffic-with-UnBounce-lg.jpg 1024w"  alt="Smart Traffic with UnBounce" width="707" height="841"></figure></span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Features of Smart Traffic Tool:</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">AI optimisation</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Automated CRO</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Fast results</span></li>
</ol>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>AMP landing pages</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Unbounce was only the first landing page builder which supports AMP landing pages. Accelerated Mobile pages are just designed to make the web pages faster for mobile users specially which increases loading speed to an average of just a second.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/amp-landing-page-builder.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/amp-landing-page-builder-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/amp-landing-page-builder-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/amp-landing-page-builder-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/amp-landing-page-builder-lg.png 1024w"  alt="amp landing page builder" width="714" height="546"></figure></span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Create AMP landing pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">AMP templates</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Up-to-date</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Unbounce makes it easy to create and test and <strong>optimise AMP landing pages</strong> in the same way you can do with any other page builder platform.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Lead Form Builder</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">This builder also comes with its own form builder which allows you to add lead generation forms to any pages. And also this feature included in a landing page builder.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/Lead-Form-Builder-Unbounce.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Lead-Form-Builder-Unbounce-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Lead-Form-Builder-Unbounce-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Lead-Form-Builder-Unbounce-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/34/responsive/Lead-Form-Builder-Unbounce-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Lead Form Builder Unbounce" width="713" height="335"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">You will get better results from a form builder and optimization tool that operates. And this is the area where you really need a specialist toll to maximise conversions. It also helps in integration of <strong>Leadformly with unbounce</strong> so you can embed your forms on landing pages and also any other web page outside of Unbounce.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>How much does Unbounce cost?</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Unbounce has three core plans and you can get access to most of its features across all of them.</span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Essential: $79/month</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Premium: $159/month</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Enterprise: $399+/month</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">As you can see here, pricing starts from $79 per month and the difference is how many landing pages and popups you can create. Even on the essential plan you will get a limit of 75 landing pages and eight popups or sticky bars, which will be all needed by all some smaller businesses.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Also, the essential plan doesn’t support AMP landing pages or some of the more advanced targeting settings. There are some features reserved for the enterprise plan such as audit logs, dedicated support and also page migration.</span></p>
<h6><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Final Words</strong></span></h6>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Unbounce is a great tool for building landing pages to promote your products and increase the conversion rates many times and also there is various features you will never see in other platforms as Unbounce itself mainly a landing page builder so we can’t say it is bad, above review written by using and experienced about its features itself.</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>ClickFunnels Review 2020 | Pros, Cons, Features</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankit.digital/clickfunnels-review.html"/>
        <id>https://ankit.digital/clickfunnels-review.html</id>
            <category term="Reviews"/>
            <category term="Landing Page"/>
            <category term="Digital Marketing"/>
            <category term="ClickFunnels Reveiw"/>

        <updated>2020-10-07T02:08:34+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/Clickfunnels-Reviews.png" alt="" />
                    Introduction to ClickFunelsClickfunnels provides you tools and strategies at one place to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/Clickfunnels-Reviews.png" alt="" />
                <h2><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Introduction to ClickFunels</strong></span></h2>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Clickfunnels</strong> provides you tools and strategies at one place to help your business grow with promotions and landing pages. </span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With the help of ClickFunnels, you can build awesome landing pages, quick sales funnels that convert customers for you, Smart Shopping carts in just 1 click, email marketing, and Facebook marketing automation at the same place.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/clickfunnels-review.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/responsive/clickfunnels-review-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/responsive/clickfunnels-review-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/responsive/clickfunnels-review-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/responsive/clickfunnels-review-lg.png 1024w"  alt="clickfunnels review" width="710" height="296"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With ClickFunnels, you can generate new leads that you can connect with, and also create simple funnels that capture your visitor’s contact information and their messages so that you can generate new leads to follow-up with again and again also after they leave your web page.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">If you are in touch with the world of <strong>digital marketing</strong>, you should have at least heard about ClickFunnels, the landing page builder that was helping online sales funnels. In this review, we will take you deep into the <strong>Pros and Cons to ClickFunnels</strong> if it is legitimate business marketing software or not.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Clickfunnels has created itself as a pretty big name since it started, as it was one of the largest marketing software as a services company. I think it is no surprise why people love Clickfunnels as it is all about making money for its users. More specifically, it’s about giving business software that helps them to turn their website’s visitors into customers and then conversions. There is no wonder ClickFunnels has grown so much and all-time higher in the list of landing page builders and marketing software in such a short period of time.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">In this review, we will go through the gist of Clickfunnels like what it is, the positives and the negatives, the features, customer service, and more. I am making this review on the basis of my own experience using ClickFunnels’ startup plan which itself includes coreClickFunnels features and other special and unique features.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>ClickFunnels Review Highlights</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Here is a list of ClickFunnels’ review highlights on which we are going to know more in this review:</span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">ClickFunnels is a nice landing page builder, with an easy drag and drop editor.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Very Easy and various integrations that allow you to capture emails and take payments inside the ClickFunnels.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Built with A/B Testing capabilities.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Easy to learn and use.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Focused on making its users more money.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">They offer a free trial of two weeks.</span></li>
</ol>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/ClickFunnels-Review-Highlights.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/responsive/ClickFunnels-Review-Highlights-xs.jpg 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/responsive/ClickFunnels-Review-Highlights-sm.jpg 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/responsive/ClickFunnels-Review-Highlights-md.jpg 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/responsive/ClickFunnels-Review-Highlights-lg.jpg 1024w"  alt="ClickFunnels Review Highlights" width="723" height="379"></figure></span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>What is ClickFunnels?</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Clickfunnels started in 2014, but in just 3 years it’s been in the words of Forbes, “silently revolutionizing the online marketing industry.” With ClickFunnels, it makes you easier for businesses and entrepreneurs to sell online using this with the ease of complicated marketing technology, which is called sales funnels.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Clickfunnels Founded by Russell Brunson who is as famous as his creation, and for a good reason. He’s made a fortune not just only for ClickFunnels, but other marketing adventures. He played around with email marketing and eventually began to master sales funnels.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">ClickFunnels started out as a way to help Brunson and his team to create funnels more quickly for different ventures as usually, it takes over a week or more to develop funnels. So they realized their creation can be useful to others and then they have launched ClickFunnels as its name means just <strong>click and make your funnels</strong> it works also in just some steps only.</span></p>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>What Are Funnels? How Sales Funnels Work?</strong></span></h5>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">In digital marketing, it is a process that can take people who don’t know you and convert them as your customers, which is known as a marketing funnel. In e-commerce, sales funnel is a series of steps designed to guide visitors to the checkout page.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Step1:</strong> Imagine a funnel.</span><br><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Step2:</strong> Imagine this funnel will be helpful for your website visitors.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Your site visitors are looking around by checking things out. And with a sales funnel you can get your website visitors to the right place for what they actually want to purchase.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">ClickFunnels is created to save your time and energy like if you want to create funnels for yourself and develop it for yourself then it requires a lot of technological proficiency and also maybe some other third-party applications, so it this respect ClickFunnels Succeeds.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>What ClickFunnels can do for you?</strong></span></h3>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Pros of ClickFunnels</strong></span></h3>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Makes you money</strong></span></h5>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">One of the best things about ClickFunnels is its focus on making money for its users. They make it very easy to use and make your account and put your content and start taking payments. But maybe it can take some hours to figure out most of what you need.</span></p>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Drag and Drop Page Builder</strong></span></h5>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">There are very few features that are very useful here. I really like how easy it is to duplicate pages and the fact is I can save templates to use them later again. Their page builder is a very important feature, and they have pulled it off. When you get used to it, it is an easy to use drag and drop page builder.</span></p>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>A/B Testing</strong></span></h5>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With ClickFunnels you will get a free A/B testing tool which is great itself to test your landing pages on various platforms also. All you need to do is duplicate a page and make your changes and choose the traffic you want to see version A or B.</span></p>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Various Selection of Integrations</strong></span></h5>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">ClickFunnels handles API Integrations well. Email and payment processors are not too good but they are working reliably and are easier to manage.</span></p>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>WordPress Integration Plugin</strong></span></h5>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">You will also get a WordPress plugin that can let you add ClickFunnels pages to your WordPress website and use it for your marketing. It saves a lot of time and is less than working between ClickFunnels and WordPress without a plugin. The ClickFunnels WordPress Plugin is also rated about 4.4 stars in WordPress Plugin store and has about 20k active installations.</span></p>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>All in one</strong></span></h5>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">From ClickFunnels you can build your landing pages, create various forms and order forms, and send marketing emails all from one platform. All of this really does save your time and money, various resources you would otherwise need to spend on many developers, CSS, hosting configurations, and more.</span></p>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Reasonable Value</strong></span></h5>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">If you have more than 20000 visitors and need over 100 pages then ClickFunnels Platinum might not be too much.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">ClickFunnels is not perfect but it does a great job of packaging great tools together and making them accessible.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Cons of ClickFunnels</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">I have some bad news, not much but still, there are few areas that need to work on ClickFunnels. Our review can’t be completed without looking at the ugly side as well.</span></p>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Overpriced?</strong></span></h5>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">A very small drawback is the price. There are only three pricing options like $97/month, $297/month, and $2,497/month. In this tool, this is not a big deal just another investment in your business, and as I have said above you will get a good package for it.</span></p>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Customer Service</strong></span></h5>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Customer support is good but in my experience, they have been fine with a basic question but if you will ask them more difficult things especially about more advanced features they can’t be very helpful.</span></p>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Too </strong><span style="font-size: 18.3848px;">Templates</span></span></h5>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">This one is not on ClickFunnels but more on the community. While you have the ability to customize with ClickFunnels, many people use similar designs. By considering the popularity of ClickFunnels, this has to be a large amount of ClickFunnels looks good.</span></p>
<h5><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Bugs</strong></span></h5>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">ClickFunnels will go down or experience some errors. This doesn’t happen any time but it does. If you are investing a lot in advertising and driving traffic to your funnels and a ClickFunnels glitch brings your pages down for even a few hours you can lose a lot of money.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>ClickFunnels Pricing – How much is Clickfunnels?</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">ClickFunnels have two plans which are ClickFunnels Standard Plan and their ClickFunnels Platinum Plan. ClickFunnels is $97 per month and Platinum comes in at $297 per month. And if you want to try all its features you will get a 14 days free trial to try their services, so at the end you don’t need to commit to an expensive plan. If you will pay annually instead of monthly then you will get two months free in $997 for ClickFunnels and $2997 for platinum plan.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">If you will compare ClickFunnels with LeadPages, a similar service which starts at $25 per month but it is important to keep in mind about ClickFunnels main service is to create funnels for you with more efficiency and it does a good job in this. I can consider it a good investment.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">The main difference between an entry level account and a premium account are :</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">The standard plan gets the main service the funnel builder with various limitations on the amount of pages, visits and custom domains which is only 3 and only some of the full list features.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">But both the plans have unlimited contacts, unlimited members can be added and all the advanced funnels, A/B Split tests and a few other features which can be helpful to create your own  sales funnels.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>What is FunnelFlix?</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">ClickFunnels Founder, originally made a lot of his money by selling information products and online courses. It seems that ClickFunnels is trying to launch the NetFlix model with FunnelFlix but with online courses, in my opinion is confusing when you are just trying to use the software for marketing services. There is some good content but it is just too much.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Features Overview of ClickFunnels</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Here’s the full list of StartUp features:</span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">20 funnels</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">100 pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">20,000 visitors</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">unlimited contacts</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">3 custom domains</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">A/B split tests</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Email integrations</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Optin funnels</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">ClickPops</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">ClickOptin</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">All advanced funnels</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Sales funnels</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Membership funnels</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited members</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Auto webinar funnels</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Hangout funnels</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Order pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Upsell pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Downsale pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Share your funnels</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">1 SMTP integration</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">1 billing integration per type</span></li>
</ol>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>ClickFunnels Page Builder</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">We can say this is the main feature of ClickFunnels, so I would like to devote special attention to it. ClickFunnels have a solid landing page builder. ClickFunnels distances itself from page building software and advertises its funnel creating software but its landing page builder is also very easy to use and it includes various elements which can convert customers for you easily.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/clickfunnels-templates.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/responsive/clickfunnels-templates-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/responsive/clickfunnels-templates-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/responsive/clickfunnels-templates-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/responsive/clickfunnels-templates-lg.png 1024w"  alt="clickfunnels templates" width="714" height="363"></figure>You can also save various templates and make personal page templates and it's very easy to find them, as you can see toggle with basic settings and you can open them in the editor.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/ClickFunnels-Editor.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/responsive/ClickFunnels-Editor-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/responsive/ClickFunnels-Editor-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/responsive/ClickFunnels-Editor-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/33/responsive/ClickFunnels-Editor-lg.png 1024w"  alt="ClickFunnels Editor" width="703" height="353"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Once you will open your pages in the editor, you will basically now go to work with a drag and drop builder. It is complicated but not more than other page builders but still it can be easier to use.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>ClickFunnels Integrations</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">ClickFunnels has very few partners you can add to your integrations quickly. Here is complete list of integration that was provided by ClickFunnels:</span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Active Campaign</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Aweber</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Constant Contact</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Convertkit</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Drip</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">GetResponse</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">GoToWebinar</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">GVO PureLeverage</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">HTML Form</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">HubSpot</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">InfusionSoft</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Interspice</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Mad Mimi</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">MailChimp</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Maropost</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Ontraport</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">SalesForce</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Sendlane</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">ShipStation</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Shopify</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Twilio</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Webinar Jam Studio</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">YouZign</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Here is the list of payment gateways you add with ClickFunnels:</span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Stripe</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Infusionsoft</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Warriorplus</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">JVZoo</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">ClickBank</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Taxamo</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Ontraport</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Blue Snap</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Easy Pay Direct</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">NMI</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Recurly</span></li>
</ol>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Ease of Use of ClickFunnels</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">ClickFunnels is much easier than creating funnels on your own and developing them. They have various amounts of documentation and it may not be perfect but it can cover most of the questions and you can always contact customer service  if you need any answer about your query and any issues.</span></p>
<h6><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Conclusion</strong></span></h6>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">So we have reached the conclusion, with my point of view, it means 4 out of 5 stars!! It was very useful and easier to use and also it is worth trying out.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">ClickFunnels succeeds in their core objective to make it easier for you to <strong>funnel traffic</strong> and reach higher conversion rates.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">If you are looking first for an easy but solid sales solution or landing page editor then ClickFunnels is a very good tool.</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>LeadPages Review 2020 | Pros, Cons, Features and Comparisons</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankit.digital/leadpages-review.html"/>
        <id>https://ankit.digital/leadpages-review.html</id>
            <category term="Review"/>
            <category term="LeadPages"/>
            <category term="Landing Page"/>
            <category term="Internet Marketing"/>
            <category term="Digital Marketing"/>
            <category term="Adwords"/>

        <updated>2020-10-07T02:08:34+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/Leadpages-REVIEW.jpg" alt="" />
                    Hello Guys!! Today we are going to discuss the most popular landing&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/Leadpages-REVIEW.jpg" alt="" />
                <p><span style="color: #000000;">Hello Guys!! Today we are going to discuss the most popular landing page builder <strong>LeadPages</strong> for any businesses. It’s the most effective and affordable way for businesses to connect with an audience to collect leads and close sales with popups and alert bars easily.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Leadpages sounds like landing page builders on the market with leads and conversion by pages. So, today in this review, we are going to take a closer look at this platform where it shines and why it was overrated in comparison with other tools you have.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With leadpages, you can build popups, alert bars, landing pages, and build websites with awesome designs and easy controls.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With the help of leadpages, you can get your business online and grow it in a very easy manner.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">You can websites without knowing coding and landing pages to engage audiences with just one click.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Features of Leadpages</strong></span></h3>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Create High-Converting Websites and Landing Pages</strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">You can easily publish your webpages in just some minutes. Start with conversion-optimized with mobile-friendly templates. Then you can customize it with easy drag and drop builder and also then you can launch a professional landing page or website which is just designed to convert leads.</span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/Create-High-Converting-Websites-and-Landing-Pages.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Create-High-Converting-Websites-and-Landing-Pages-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Create-High-Converting-Websites-and-Landing-Pages-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Create-High-Converting-Websites-and-Landing-Pages-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Create-High-Converting-Websites-and-Landing-Pages-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Create High-Converting Websites and Landing Pages" width="801" height="563"></figure><strong>Count every piece of Content</strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">When you are posting any content then you can optimize them with the use of leadpages elements for your business purpose. With this, you can convert your traffic into leads and conversion with the help of complete conversion tools like alert bars, pop-ups, Opt-in text, and more.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/Count-every-piece-of-Content.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Count-every-piece-of-Content-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Count-every-piece-of-Content-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Count-every-piece-of-Content-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Count-every-piece-of-Content-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Count every piece of Content" width="753" height="543"></figure></span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Insights for all of your landing pages</strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With this you can optimize your every aspect of marketing campaigns with the help of analytics dashboard, A/B Split tests, and real-time conversion tips.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/insights.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/insights-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/insights-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/insights-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/insights-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Insights" width="661" height="529"></figure></span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Publish unlimited Landing pages and also get unlimited templates<br></strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">As some platforms having limited templates and publishing limits but on leadpages, you can get unlimited templates with unlimited publishing options. They don’t charge more for the number of leads collected and a number of pages published.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/Publish-unlimited-Landing-pages.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Publish-unlimited-Landing-pages-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Publish-unlimited-Landing-pages-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Publish-unlimited-Landing-pages-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Publish-unlimited-Landing-pages-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Publish unlimited Landing pages" width="675" height="497"></figure></span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Easy Integration with apps<br></strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With leadpages, you can easily integrate with your favorite apps within a minute with the help of various data slots like Google Analytics, Facebook, stripe and MailChimp, and more.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/easy-integrations.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/easy-integrations-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/easy-integrations-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/easy-integrations-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/easy-integrations-lg.png 1024w"  alt="easy integrations" width="731" height="267"></figure></span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Customer Support</strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Leadpages provides world-class support for their customers like a direct phone call, email or chat, etc, that’s why you can’t be stuck anywhere.</span></p>
<h2><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Leadpages Overview</strong></span></h2>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With leadpages, you can create easily digital content without any coding knowledge or Graphic designing knowledge just drag and drop page builder can help you get better with leadpages.</span><br><br><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Things or features you can get from Leadpages are:</strong></span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Get your business online</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Collect Leads</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Sell Products and Services</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Optimize and Grow</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">SEO-friendly pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Free hosting</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Tracking &amp; analytics</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Device-specific preview</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">99.9% uptime</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Automatic SSL encryption</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">GDPR compliance</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Top speed &amp; reliability</span></li>
</ol>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Builder Features:</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Digital file hosting &amp; delivery</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Duplicate &amp; edit</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Easy drag-and-drop interface</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Custom social media preview</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Device-specific preview</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Custom &amp; hidden form fields</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Image library</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Lead backup</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Lead gen form builder</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Lead notifications</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Lead routing</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Mobile responsive pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Online sales &amp; payments</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Page grouping</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Revert to last published version</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited page publishing</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited traffic &amp; leads</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Tracking and third-party analytics</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Widgets</span></li>
</ol>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Conversion Tools:</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">10 Opt-in text campaigns</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Clear campaign ROI</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Email trigger links</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Exit-intent pop-ups</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Real-time optimization tips</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Real-time analytics</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Third-party analytics</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited A/B split testing</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited alert bars</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited pop-ups</span></li>
</ol>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Design and Templates:</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Section templates</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Shutterstock Premium Images</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Built-in icon library</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">OpenTable embed widget</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Countdown timers</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Custom branding</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Customizable templates</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Design from a blank page</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Global page style settings</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">HTML &amp; Custom Code Editing</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Keyboard shortcuts</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Mobile-responsive</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Social share buttons</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Thank-you &amp; confirmation pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Device-specific display</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Video embed widget</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">On-page section links</span></li>
</ol>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Support Features:</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">1-on-1 Quickstart call</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Free Leadpages Virtual Workshops</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Phone, chat, &amp; email support</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Knowledgebase</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Weekly group coaching</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">World-class tech support</span></li>
</ol>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Integration Features:</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">40+ Standard integrations</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Advanced integrations</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Major email service integrations</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Zapier integration</span></li>
</ol>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Publishing Features:</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Connect your domain</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Flexible publishing options</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Free hosting</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Simple WordPress plugin</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Free Leadpages domain</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited publishing to your website</span></li>
</ol>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Security Features:</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Automatic SSL encryption</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Subaccount login</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">GDPR Compliance</span></li>
</ol>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Website Builder Features:</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Drag-and-drop website builder</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Website preview</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Mobile-responsive menu</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Drop-down menu</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Drag-and-drop website menu</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Integrated conversion tools</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Website SEO</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Website templates</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Pre-built add-on pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Built-in 404 page</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Global website footer</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Website style settings</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Website publishing</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Free Custom Domain (With Annual Purchase)</span></li>
</ol>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Website Builder</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Easiest Website Builder with most effective in leads and conversion and get your traffic converted into sales.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/Leadpages-as-a-website-builder.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-as-a-website-builder-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-as-a-website-builder-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-as-a-website-builder-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-as-a-website-builder-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Leadpages as a website builder" width="708" height="494"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With <strong>LeadPages website builder</strong>, you can create high converting websites without coding customization, and also you can build your business with the help of this website builder.</span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Features of Website Builder</strong><strong>:</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Create beautiful websites with conversion powers.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Start with converting templates.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Easily save time with pre-built blocks and web-pages.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Code-free Customizations</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Get Complete conversion toolkit</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Fast Loading Speed</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">100% Mobile Responsive</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Streamlined analytics dashboard</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Built-in SEO</span></li>
</ol>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Landing Pages</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Build unlimited landing pages with the help of built-in conversion elements with page performance analytics before publishing.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/Landing-Pages-builder-in-LeadPages.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Landing-Pages-builder-in-LeadPages-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Landing-Pages-builder-in-LeadPages-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Landing-Pages-builder-in-LeadPages-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Landing-Pages-builder-in-LeadPages-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Landing Pages builder in LeadPages" width="701" height="491"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With the help of this, you can easily DIY <strong>high conversion landing pages</strong> to grow your business with clicks into the customers.</span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Features of Landing Page Builder</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Built-in conversion guidance</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited lead collection &amp; traffic</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited page publishing</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unparalleled page load speed</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Code-free drag-and-drop customizations</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Mobile-responsive</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Features &amp; functionality to fit any need</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Make the most of your advertising budget</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Grow your email list 2x faster</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Save time with integrations</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Opt-in pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Thank-you pages &amp; confirmation pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Sales pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Checkout pages</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With this, you can easily become a true marketing professional when you will use various leadpages integrations that connect your lead generation tools and marketing automation platforms. <strong>Leadpages landing pages</strong> that capture email addresses inside segmented lists and also nurture your new leads with email marketing which works for you like all the time sales team.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Pop-Ups</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With Pop-up which triggers click, time delays, or exit intent and adds them to any web page within just some clicks.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/Pop-Ups-Builder-in-LeadPages.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Pop-Ups-Builder-in-LeadPages-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Pop-Ups-Builder-in-LeadPages-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Pop-Ups-Builder-in-LeadPages-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Pop-Ups-Builder-in-LeadPages-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Pop-Ups Builder in LeadPages" width="702" height="485"></figure></span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Features of Pop-Ups Builder</strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With the <strong>Pop-Up builder</strong>, you can easily capture your audiences with their interests by targeting their interests with the help of email signup forms into the popups, and also you can add these leadpages pop-ups into any webpage and landing pages.</span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Easy trigger events</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Pop-up Display Wait Time</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Exit intent</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Publish on a landing page</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Publish on a website</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Publish on WordPress</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Customize your content</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Connect your email service provider</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Landing Page Pop-ups</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Blog Sidebar Buttons</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Guest Blog Links</span></li>
</ol>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Alert Bars</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With alert bars, you can easily capture your audience’s attention to your webpage with their mobile-friendly bars and good designs and also boost conversions.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/Alert-Bars-Builders-in-LeadPages.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Alert-Bars-Builders-in-LeadPages-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Alert-Bars-Builders-in-LeadPages-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Alert-Bars-Builders-in-LeadPages-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Alert-Bars-Builders-in-LeadPages-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Alert Bars Builders in LeadPages" width="696" height="485"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Various options available to capture your audiences:</span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Mobile-friendly layouts</strong>: There are four mobile responsive layouts available which can automatically adjust to appear into the optimum position depending on users’ device screen resolution.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Text-Based Announcements</strong>: Easily announce your any exclusive or latest deals or invite your visitors to your email list by submitting a name and email address on a header.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Flexible Publishing Options</strong>: You can publish alert bars on any page or website or landing pages which allows you for the use of HTML and JS like WordPress.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Simplified Analytics</strong>: Track the performance of your alert bars into the leadpages dashboard to identify which pages are performing the best.</span></li>
</ol>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Features of Alert Bars</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Capture leads anywhere</strong>: Do you know more than 90% of your traffic is not ready to buy when they have visited your website for the first time. But with the help of alert bars, you can engage your audiences and their attention by adding alert bars into the header with sticky bars and also collect leads.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Select a layout:</strong> You can start with a pre-designed, mobile responsive layout that can remain sticky to the top of your website or the bottom.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Customize your content</strong>: Easily change the color of your bars, include a hyperlink, forms, or CTA buttons.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Connect your email service provider</strong>: Automatically integrate your subscribers directly to your email list into your ESP app.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Publish</strong>: Easily publish your alert bar on a page or website by pasting a snippet of code.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Create an opt-in opportunity</strong>: Include a simple opt-in form and CTA button to boost conversions and reduce bounce rates.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Drive traffic to a landing page</strong>: If you want to announce a discount sale or want to send traffic to another post then you can add headlines without affecting user experience.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Convert blog readers into leads</strong>: Easily convert your readers into leads by adding newsletter and subscription promotion into an opt-in bar.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Promote an offer</strong>: If you want to put the spotlight on your coupon code or offer then you can also do so by showcasing it in your alert bars.</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">More than 180+ Landing page templates are available to use into leadpages for pre-built features for landing pages you want to build.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">And more than 15+ website templates are available to use into leadpages website builder for pre-built features to build your awesome designed website.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Leadpages Pros</strong></span></h3>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Affordable</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Easy to use</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Quick Creation</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Filter Templates</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Integration Options</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">No limitations of Traffic</span></li>
</ol>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Leadpages Cons</strong></span></h3>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">No Enterprise Options</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">On standard plan A/B Testing</span></li>
</ol>
<h2><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Pricing of LeadPages</strong></span></h2>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Leadpages Standard ($37/mo, paid annually)</strong></span></h3>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited Pages, Traffic, &amp; Leads</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited Pop-ups</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited Alert Bars</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Free Hosting</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Connect 1 Domain</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">200+ Free Templates(Mobile-Responsive)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">40+ Standard Integrations</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Facebook &amp; Instagram AdBuilder</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Tech Support (via Email)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Weekly Group Coaching</span></li>
</ul>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Leadpages Pro ($79/mo, paid annually)</strong></span></h3>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">All Standard features</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Online Sales and Payments</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited A/B Split Testing</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Email Trigger Links</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">10 Opt-in Text Campaigns</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Special Discounts with partner companies</span></li>
</ul>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Leadpages Advanced ($321/mo, paid annually)</strong></span></h3>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">All Standard and Pro features</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Advanced Integrations</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">5 Free Sub Accounts</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">50 Extra Opt-in TextCampaigns</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">1-on-1 Quick Start Call</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Leadpages Virtual Workshop</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>All Plans are included below features:</strong></span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Leadpages site builder</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited landing pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited leads &amp; traffic</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited pop-ups &amp; alert bars</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Rapid page load speed</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Lead notifications</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Mobile responsive pages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Lead magnet hosting &amp; delivery</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">SEO capability</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Real-time analytics</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">40+ Integrations</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">GDPR compliance</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">There is one huge advantage of Leadpages which is it has over the competition is that fact which is no restriction on traffic, regardless of which version you use. You don’t want to upgrade your plan to increase your traffic limit.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">You don’t have a limitation with leadpages, which is awesome if you have a lot of traffic coming to your site.</span></p>
<h2><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Comparison with Leadpages and Other Competitors</strong></span></h2>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Leadpages vs Unbounce</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">If you are looking for a comparison of Leadpages vs Unbounce software, then you should also know that these both are helpful in building landing pages.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/Leadpages-vs-unbounce.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-vs-unbounce-xs.jpg 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-vs-unbounce-sm.jpg 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-vs-unbounce-md.jpg 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-vs-unbounce-lg.jpg 1024w"  alt="Leadpages vs Unbounce" width="740" height="316"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">While there are numerous conversion channels used by business owners for their websites, landing pages are much popular because of their efficiency.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Differences between Leadpages and Unbounce are:</span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Leadpages allow you to do flexible integration into your existing site but Unbounce requires users to use a subdomain on their site.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Leadpages have a very cheaper price than Unbounce starts at $99 per month.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Leadpages offers full integration with Facebook but Unbounce can’t let you integrate with Facebook.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Leadpages offer you to create an unlimited number of pages but Unbounce has limitations based on pricings.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Leadpages Limits A/B Testing to higher plans but <strong>Unbounce</strong> enables A/B testing to all their plans.</span></li>
</ol>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Leadpages vs Instapage</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Let us discuss the core features of both, then you can understand the difference between both landing page builders.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/Leadpages-vs-instapage.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-vs-instapage-xs.jpg 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-vs-instapage-sm.jpg 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-vs-instapage-md.jpg 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-vs-instapage-lg.jpg 1024w"  alt="Leadpages vs Instapage" width="794" height="339"></figure></span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Leadpages core features:</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Drag and Drop Editing- Build landing pages with easy drag and drop and visual previews.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">150+ Free Landing Page Templates</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Easy Integration with various marketing tools</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Free Hosting for landing pages.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Analytics for performance</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Easy Website integrations with HTML or a WordPress Plugin</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Full website building</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Alert Bars</span></li>
</ol>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Instapage core features:</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Grid-Free drag and Drop Editing Builder</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">200+ Free Templates</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Various Integration</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Instapage hosts landing pages and make it easy to run on your own domain with WordPress plugin.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Simple A/B Tests</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Analytics with third-party analytics service connections</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Easy Collaboration Tools</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Both tools can create 100% responsive landing pages, so you never need to worry about visitors on various devices having poor experiences.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Instapage</strong> give you more control over how the responsive design of your page looks because its editor lets you make separate edits for various devices.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Leadpages vs Elementor</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Let us explain the comparison of both landing page builders with Some key points.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/Leadpages-vs-Elementor.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-vs-Elementor-xs.jpg 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-vs-Elementor-sm.jpg 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-vs-Elementor-md.jpg 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-vs-Elementor-lg.jpg 1024w"  alt="Leadpages vs Elementor" width="789" height="337"></figure></span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Leadpages Key Points:</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Pricing starts at $25.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Pricing Model: Monthly or Annually</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Integrations: WordPress, Weebly, Squarespace, Drupal, Joomla, Facebook, Twitter, Linkedin, Google plus, Stripe, Paypal, Hubspot, Facebook ads, Google Adwords, Mailchimp, Sendreach, Getresponse, Drip, Convertkit, Shopify and more.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Prominent Clients: Forbes, Techcrunch, and Fortune, etc.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Available Devices: Windows, Mac, iPhone, Android, Web-Based.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Available For: Small Business, Medium Business, and Large Business.</span></li>
</ol>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Elementor Key Points:</strong></span></h4>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Pricing starts at $49.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Pricing Model: Free or Annual Subscription.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Integrations: It works with WordPress Plugins and widgets. It also integrates with CRMs and email marketing services as well as with Facebook and woocommerce only.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Prominent Clients: Siteground.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Available Devices: Windows, Linux, Mac, and Web-based.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Available For: Small business, Medium Business, Large Business, and Freelancers.</span></li>
</ol>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Leadpages vs Thrive Architect</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Let us explain key differences between thrive landing pages and leadpages.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/Leadpages-vs-Thrive-Architect.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-vs-Thrive-Architect-xs.jpg 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-vs-Thrive-Architect-sm.jpg 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-vs-Thrive-Architect-md.jpg 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/32/responsive/Leadpages-vs-Thrive-Architect-lg.jpg 1024w"  alt="Leadpages vs Thrive Architect" width="754" height="322"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Leadpages and <a href="https://ankit.digital/thrive-themes-review.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" style="color: #000000;">Thrive Architect</a> are two different products. They are different from their core but still do many of the same things. The biggest difference between thrive architect and leadpages are:</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>“Leadpages is a hosted Solution but thrive architect is a WordPress plugin”</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">If you don’t have any website but still want to build landing pages then you can use leadpages but if you want to use a thrive Architect, then you need the self-hosted website running WordPress as it is web’s most widely used CMS.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">You can’t use a <strong>thrive architect</strong> if your website doesn’t use WordPress. If that’s the case, then leadpages is a better solution for you.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">As a beginner, a bigger decision factor for selecting one of the best is the price, especially if the products are similar feature-wise. For a budget-conscious buyer then a thrive architect is clearly a better choice for building a landing page.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">The thrive membership and <strong>leadpages pro</strong> is a much more interesting and helpful comparison if you are looking to grow your online business for the long term. There are the products which are especially focused on generating more leads for your online business than just landing pages, they both require payments.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Thrive Membership Comes in <strong>$228/year</strong> for 25 websites which include:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Access to complete Thrive Tool Suite like Thrive Architect, Thrive Leads, Thrive Website Themes, Thrive ultimatum, etc.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited Support</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Unlimited Updates for the membership period.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Leadpages Pro comes in <strong>$576/Year</strong> with everything in the standard plan also some extra features like:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">A/B Testing &amp; Leaddigits.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Access to affiliate program &amp; Partner Discounts</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Upload Custom Landing Page Templates</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Priority Support and Live Chat.</span></li>
</ul>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Flexibility in Thrive Membership:</strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">When it comes to customization then thrive membership suite excels. There are beautiful, pre-designed pages, opt-in forms ready for traffic with just a few clicks, and changes to the texts and product image replacement.</span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Flexibility in Leadpages Pro:</strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">When it comes to page customization, leadpages have two types of templates which are standard and drag-and-drop.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">The standard templates don’t allow for much customization but in drag-and-drop templates clearly allows you to customize everything you want.</span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Conclusion</strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Leadpages should be your better choice when you are going to build your online business and want to get more growth then it can help you in many ways as explained above. It can help you to improve your website’s engagement and sales with upcoming traffic. Leadpages are much better in pricing as well with others in the competition. It also allows you integration with many services that can help you to increase engagement with users or visitors.</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Ultimate Guide to Google Webmasters 2020</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankit.digital/guide-to-google-webmasters.html"/>
        <id>https://ankit.digital/guide-to-google-webmasters.html</id>
            <category term="Technical SEO"/>
            <category term="Google Webmasters Guide"/>
            <category term="Google Search Console"/>
            <category term="Advanced SEO Techniques"/>

        <updated>2020-10-07T02:08:34+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/Guide-To-Google-Search-Console.png" alt="Guide To Google Search Console" />
                    What is Google Search Console?Google Search Console formerly known for Google Webmaster&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/Guide-To-Google-Search-Console.png" alt="Guide To Google Search Console" />
                <h2><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>What is Google Search Console?</strong></span></h2>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Google Search Console formerly known for Google Webmaster Tools which is a free platform and it can be used by anyone who owns a Gmail account with a website for which he/she wants to monitor how Google views their website and also with Google Search Console it can optimize its organic presence on the search engine. Google Search Console includes viewing your referring domains, mobile website performance, rich results, and traffic queries, and most visited pages.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/Google-Search-Console.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/Google-Search-Console-xs.jpg 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/Google-Search-Console-sm.jpg 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/Google-Search-Console-md.jpg 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/Google-Search-Console-lg.jpg 1024w"  alt="Google Search Console"></figure></span></p>
<h2><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>How to add your website to Google Search Console?</strong></span></h2>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Here we will let you know how to add your website to Google Search Console. Follow the below steps:</span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Login to your Google Account. Make sure you are using your business Gmail account if its business website if it’s personal then you can use your personal account.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Go to <a href="https://search.google.com/search-console/welcome" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" style="color: #000000;">Google Search Console</a></span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Click on add property as below screenshot</span></li>
</ol>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/Add-Property-in-Search-Console.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/Add-Property-in-Search-Console-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/Add-Property-in-Search-Console-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/Add-Property-in-Search-Console-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/Add-Property-in-Search-Console-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Add Property in Google Search Console" width="753" height="347"></figure>4. Choose your property type:</span><br><span style="color: #000000;">4.1. <strong>Domain</strong>: We have to select this when we have more than 1 subdomain like if you want to add m. or www. As well then you have to select this type and do further verification.</span><br><span style="color: #000000;">4.2 <strong>URL Prefix</strong>: We have to select this when we have only one domain and then do further verification.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><br><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/property-type-selection.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/property-type-selection-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/property-type-selection-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/property-type-selection-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/property-type-selection-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Property type Selection in Google Search Console" width="735" height="473"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">5. Select the correct URL of your website.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">There are 5 types of verification methods you can verify with any of these.</span><br><span style="color: #000000;">1. HTML File</span><br><span style="color: #000000;">2. HTML Meta Tag</span><br><span style="color: #000000;">3. Google Analytics</span><br><span style="color: #000000;">4. Google Tag Manager</span><br><span style="color: #000000;">5. Domain Name Provider</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Why verification needed for Google Search Console?</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">I hope you are well known that Google search console gives you access to confidential information about your website’s performance so that you need to verify that you own that site.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">This verification gives a specific user control over a property. You must verify one owner per Google Search Console Property.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Also, note down that after verification of your property doesn’t affect your page ranking and performance in Google Search.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">It may increase your performance with more information with Google Search Console and due to this, you can rank easily in search engines.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Difference Between Owner Permission, Full Permission, and Restricted Permission</strong></span></h3>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Owner Permission</strong>: You can check all about your website, manage users, total control of all your related properties, change the settings, and access every tool. The owner can add delegated owners to the property who can’t have that much control but they can also do much and they can’t add more users without verification with any one method of verification.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Full Permission</strong>: They can check all information and also take some actions but can’t add users.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong style="font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit;">Restricted Permission</strong><span style="font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">: They can check all information related to that particular property but can’t take any action.</span></span></li>
</ol>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Features and Reporting Tools in GSC</strong></span></h3>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Robots.txt tester</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Sitemap reports and testing tool</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Coverage Report</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Performance report</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">URL Inspection Tool</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Removal Tool</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Core web vital tool</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Mobile Usability Report</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Links report</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Settings</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Security and Manual Action Report</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">International Targeting Tool</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Crawl Stats report</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Messages</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">URL Parameter</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Ad experience report</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Abusive Experience Report</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Abusive Notifications</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Testing Tools</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Other resources</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Now I am going to explain all the above tools about what they are and how you can use it to improve your website performance.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><a href="https://www.google.com/webmasters/tools/robots-testing-tool" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" style="color: #000000;">Robots.txt Tester</a>: Here you can check your robots.txt blocking or unblocking and also see how Google sees your robots.txt even you can also update from here your recent update in robots.txt.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Sitemap reports and testing tool</strong>: Here you can test all your sitemaps and also submit your sitemap. From this report, you can check when Google read your sitemap and how many links are discovered by Google from your sitemap.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Coverage Report</strong>: In this reporting tool, you can check all your website’s coverage report regarding when any error found in your website you will get a notification through your admin email or any full access user that GSC Detected coverage issue in your website. This coverage report also shows that how your website performing over the coverage of search results. Like if you have any 404 then it will show all of your pages with a soft 404 effects. Now you need to validate that you have fixed your 404 pages and made them work.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong style="font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit;">Performance Report</strong><span style="font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">: Here you can check all performance of your website from any date to any year with filter means you can check all details related to your website pages that how much they are performing to the search engine and when they are down and how many organic clicks you have got for that particular pages. In which country you have got maximum clicks, from which device you are getting most of the clicks etc.</span></span></li>
</ul>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/Performance-Report-of-Google-Search-Console.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/Performance-Report-of-Google-Search-Console-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/Performance-Report-of-Google-Search-Console-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/Performance-Report-of-Google-Search-Console-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/Performance-Report-of-Google-Search-Console-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Performance Report of Google Search Console" width="722" height="369"></figure></span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>URL Inspection Tool</strong>: From here you can inspect your web URL by putting your  URL into the box and check with Live Test about how Google views your page you will get errors to report on that page.</span></li>
</ul>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/URL-Inspection-Tool-in-Google-Search-Console.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/URL-Inspection-Tool-in-Google-Search-Console-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/URL-Inspection-Tool-in-Google-Search-Console-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/URL-Inspection-Tool-in-Google-Search-Console-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/URL-Inspection-Tool-in-Google-Search-Console-lg.png 1024w"  alt="URL Inspection Tool in GSC" width="744" height="92"></figure></span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Removal Tool</strong>: From here you can remove your outdated content, information, or any 404 pages which are not present on your website. You will see this option left side column.</span></li>
</ul>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/Removal-Tool-in-GSC.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/Removal-Tool-in-GSC-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/Removal-Tool-in-GSC-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/Removal-Tool-in-GSC-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/Removal-Tool-in-GSC-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Removal Tool in GSC" width="760" height="224"></figure></span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/How-to-request-removal.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/How-to-request-removal-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/How-to-request-removal-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/How-to-request-removal-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/How-to-request-removal-lg.png 1024w"  alt="How to request removal" width="763" height="429"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Here are two options 1) Remove this URL Only- Means you can remove only URL that you want to remove but when you have to remove URLs from any particular prefix then you have to select the second option it will remove all URLs related with that prefix.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Moving to other tools:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Core web vital tool: </strong>From here you can see how your website or its pages performing on any particular device like you will see the speed-related information about how much speed performance of your web pages on mobile and desktop and if your website is slow then you will get an error report with the URL which are slow and below the recommended value. And you need to fix them for reaching more visitors from Search Results as Google is now working with Mobile-First indexing which means you need to make your website much responsive as possible.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Mobile Usability Report</strong>: Here in this report you can check whether your website is mobile-friendly or not if something issue related to mobile usability you can get here with the problematic URL or page.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Links report</strong>: Here in this report, you can check about your top pages, linking domains or pages, external links to your URL, etc.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Settings</strong>: From here you can check who has access to your website, you can add users as well, Ownership verification details, and also from here you can update Google about you have changed the address of your website when you are going to redirect your website to another domain.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Security and Manual Action Report</strong>: Here in this report you can see two reports one is security action report in which any security-related issues found in your website then you can see here, Google will automatically define that your website’s security compromised and in manual action report you can see is your website having any spammy content which violates Google’s policies then your website’s all issues will be shown here.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong style="font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit;">International Targeting</strong><span style="font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);"> Tool: Here with this tool, you can check and target any particular country. Here you can see two options for selecting or language option if you are selected any href lang on your website then you can see here that Google detected or not if not then you have to fix it. And also here you can find a second option to select any particular country where you want to show your website, not another country.</span></span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Crawl Stats report</strong>: Here you can see your website’s crawl stats report which means you can see Googlebot’s activity in the last 90 days.</span></li>
</ul>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/crawl-stats-report-in-GSC.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/crawl-stats-report-in-GSC-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/crawl-stats-report-in-GSC-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/crawl-stats-report-in-GSC-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/30/responsive/crawl-stats-report-in-GSC-lg.png 1024w"  alt="crawl stats report in GSC" width="745" height="439"></figure></span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Messages</strong>: Here in this tool you can see all of your website’s issues or related search console messages and if Google detected any problem then you will get an email to admin email and also in this tool.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>URL Parameter</strong>: Use this feature only if you're sure how parameters work. Incorrectly excluding URLs could result in many pages disappearing from search. Means you can add parameters of the URLs which you want to make it appear on Search Engine or if you have made it wrong then it can remove your website permanently disappear from search engine.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Ad experience report</strong>: Here in this tool how your ads are behaving on different devices like desktop and mobile.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong style="font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit;">Abusive Experience Report</strong><span style="font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">: From here you can check if anyone has a complaint about your site is abusive or any abusive experience they are recognized. See the below screenshot.</span></span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Abusive Notifications</strong>: This can help you to find any abusive related notification on your website with this tool.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Testing Tools</strong>: Here in this tab you can find various tools that can help your website to perform well with various rich results tester like structured data testing tool in which you can test that Google has checked your structured data correctly and shown on search results or not. In the same tab, you will see an email markup tester tool which means you can validate your structured data contents of an HTML email.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong style="font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit;">Other resources</strong><span style="font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">: Here in this tab, you can find various Google products related to your website and with the use of these tools you can easily optimize your website, track your visits by Google Analytics. Simply you can say that these tab contents are navigation to the best Google products which can help you to get more with your website.</span></span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Conclusion</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Google Search Console Platform can help you to analyze your website and how your websites performing on <strong>Google Search</strong>. Google Search Console can help you to optimize your website as per your visitor's requirements and what they actually want you can use a performance report to view what are the queries of visitors and what they want to know from your website and with this also you can optimize your CTR %.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">And further you need any information related to Google Search Console and you have any issues on your website and any error you reported from Google Search Console then you can contact <a href="https://support.google.com/webmasters/community?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" style="color: #000000;">Google Webmasters Help Community</a></span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Shopify Review 2020 | Pros , Cons and Features</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankit.digital/shopify-reviews.html"/>
        <id>https://ankit.digital/shopify-reviews.html</id>
            <category term="Shopify Reviews"/>
            <category term="Shopify Pros and Cons"/>
            <category term="Shopify Price"/>
            <category term="Shopify Features"/>
            <category term="Reviews"/>

        <updated>2020-10-07T02:08:34+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/Shopify-Review.png" alt="Shopify Review 2020 | Pros, Cons and Features" />
                    Are you an eCommerce store owner or going to launch your first&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/Shopify-Review.png" alt="Shopify Review 2020 | Pros, Cons and Features" />
                <p><span style="color: #000000;">Are you an eCommerce store owner or going to launch your first eCommerce store? Then you have to check about which one is the best platform to launch your first store.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Here in this article, you will get to know about the best and widely used eCommerce platform <strong>Shopify and its review.</strong> </span></p>
<h2><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Introduction of Shopify</strong></span></h2>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">With <strong>Shopify</strong>, you can build an online store for any business you want to create an online website/store. Shopify can help you to build your online store more perfectly than ever with their excessive payment gateway integration without any issue.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">A lot of payment gateway integration with any type of payment accepted by you and if any issue you have then Shopify support team always available for you and also there are various blog posts available on Shopify itself to solve your problem related to Shopify and it can solve your issue immediately but I think Shopify processes are much easy and also that can easily integrate your payment gateway as a <strong>payment gateway</strong> for an online store is much problematic these days while launching an online store.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">On Shopify<strong>,</strong> you can sell any type of product like physical or digital which are downloadable. Also, there is a lot of free themes available on Shopify which can make your store more beautiful and professional.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">There is a lot of free tools or applications also available in Shopify to give your online store some extra features and also helps you to start your offline business online.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Some of the important free tools are:</span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Logo Maker</strong>- Easily create awesome logos to beautify your store and help to find your brand to your customers and search engines.</span><br><br></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Business Name Generator</strong>- Generate a business name for your business by giving your business type in the tool and the tool will generate 100 relevant names for your business.</span><br><br></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Slogan Maker</strong>- If you want to make or if you don’t have any tagline or slogan for your business then you can take help of this tool it will generate almost 1000 slogans for your business and you can use it for your business.</span><br><br></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Pay Stub Generator</strong>- Generate cloud-based pay stub for your new business for free no additional cost included.</span><br><br></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>QR Code Generator</strong>- Generate QR Code for your business easily.</span><br><br></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Terms and conditions generator</strong>- If you are in hurry and don’t have much time or your English is weak then you can use this tool to generate your terms and conditions for your upcoming customers for your online business easily.</span><br><br></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Business Card Maker</strong>- If you need a business card for your business and want to promote your store offline or physical then business cards much useful for you and if you have no knowledge of designing then this tool can be useful for you.</span><br><br></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Gift Certificate Generator</strong>- Generate gift certificates for building your customers more loyal and spread the love for your brand to your customers.</span><br><br></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Invoice Generator</strong>- After any purchase, send the free automatic invoice to your customer for free or also you can build or generate the invoice for future use with the help of this tool into Shopify itself.</span><br><br></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Purchase Order Template<br><br></strong></span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Privacy Policy Generator</strong>- Generate a free privacy policy for your online store easily and save your time.</span><br><br></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Refund Policy Generator</strong>- Generate refund policy for your website easily and free which may help your customer to make trust in your online store that you are careful in increasing your brand visibility and customer engagement.</span><br><br></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Barcode Generator</strong>- Track and organize your products with unique barcodes with the help of a free barcode generator tool.</span><br><br></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Image resizer</strong>- Resize your product images into Shopify itself for free.</span><br><br></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong style="font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit;">Discount Calculator</strong><span style="font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">- Calculate your discounts for your customers easily into Shopify itself and it is easy for your customers too.</span></span></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">There are eight types of store examples or themes available for Shopify online store:</span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Home &amp; Decor</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Crafts &amp; Books</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Fashion</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Accessories</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Food &amp; Drinks</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Electronics</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Artworks</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Merchandise</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Shopify can be used for some reasons also if you want to:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Start your online business</strong>- You can create a business when you have a fresh Idea or looking for new ways to earn money.</span><br><br></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Move your business online</strong>- You can move your offline retail business to an online platform with an easy method and one-click setup.</span><br><br></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;"><strong style="font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit;">Switch to Shopify</strong><span style="font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">- Easy switch to Shopify no matter which eCommerce platform you are using currently.</span></span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Shopify is one of the platforms with all the eCommerce and point of sale features you need to start and grow your business.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Why Use Shopify?</strong></span></h3>
<ol>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Online Store.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Retail easy</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Buy Button</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Social selling features including buyable pins, Facebook shop, and messenger.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Amazon Integration</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">The popularity of Shopify is growing day by day just because its user-friendliness, the choice of templates and flexibility, and also SEO Features are awesome and all these don’t need any technical knowledge to use it.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Simply as per their features and users, Shopify wants to build a hassle-free platform for just setting eCommerce businesses where anyone can sell, ship, and manage their orders or products easily.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">It doesn’t matter if you are just going to start or if you are looking for a way to take your business to the next level then this review can help you the most for choosing the right for your online business.</span></p>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>History of Shopify</strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Shopify was founded by 3 people named Tobias Lutke, Scott Lake, and Daniel Weinand in 2006 but the process of defining and creating Shopify already started some years before.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Overall it started in 2004 when they are searching for an e-commerce platform that looks like they want so they decided to create one for themselves and due to this situation Shopify being into the process. However, during this time, Shopify existed only for an online store only not you know today as a platform for creating an online eCommerce store.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">At that time, Shopify is actually known for SnowDevil where founders of Shopify selling snowboards.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Shopify got a lot of recognition from many sources, which let it to bigger growth. In the year 2012, Shopify was named Canada’s smartest company. And also in 2013, when they made $1.68 billion in sales only. By 2015, sales became more than just double.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">In simple words, Shopify is an eCommerce website builder and it allows you to easily set up your online store and sells whatever you want physical and downloadable or digital products.  You can easily organize your products, customize your store design with available themes for free and accept payments online, and credit cards, and track the orders within Shopify’s dashboard.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Shopify is a better solution for an eCommerce website that provides ready-made online shops you can customize to your content. It has that much capacity to be the feature and out of the box, but not at the expense of drag times.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Payment plans are based on monthly billing, but when you are running a store with profit then these little costs should be negligible with the time being.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Using Shopify is very easy to start the work and setup. You just need to sign up, then you are taken by the hand with step by step process.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">At the start, you will get over 100 optimized online store designs and you need to choose the better one which can be useful for your business category. These store designs are optimized by professionals to generate good conversion rates from your visitors.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/Shopify-Pre-designed-store-templates.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Shopify-Pre-designed-store-templates-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Shopify-Pre-designed-store-templates-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Shopify-Pre-designed-store-templates-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Shopify-Pre-designed-store-templates-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Shopify Pre-designed store templates" width="652" height="318"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">And one more thing Shopify does include web hosting which is another benefit of it. This means you don’t need to login to another external web hosting to manage your files you will get all your important and required things into the dashboard and for security, your store was directly hosted on cloud servers which is unknown to anyone.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Shopify uses an optimized server that is built for eCommerce in mind. And also Shopify is known for a cloud-based eCommerce platform.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Is Shopify really easy and simple to use?</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">The platform of Shopify doesn’t share the problem. You don’t need to be an expert to set up a shop and anyone can easily launch an online retail store within a matter of minutes.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Third-Party Integration with Shopify</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Shopify also offers easy integration with <strong>HubSpot</strong> plugin that helps you to get more traffic to your store, which will then increase your revenue much more.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">There are many more benefits that come with this integration such as syncing information like products and orders and also getting insight into the new trends of marketing and expanding business in various areas.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Integration is a <strong>Shoelace</strong> which enables you to retarget your customers to keep them engaged and introduce new ads that are designed for your customer base. Another useful advantage is that you can connect this with your social media platform to sync all of your messages.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Klaviyo</strong> is known for its personalized marketing that can boost your sales and engage subscribers and add automated flows, send personalized coupons, and also an alert for the availability of products in stock.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">You also have the option to connect your Shopify store to social media platforms like Facebook for facebook shopping and also Google Shopping integration made it easy to sell your products directly from Google itself by Shopping features.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>How Does Shopify Works?</strong></span></h3>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">After filling the signup form (Name, Email, etc.), you will get to use Shopify’s to set up the process of your eCommerce store. Firstly they will ask you about the things for which you’re going to be selling:</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/signup-process-of-shopify-store.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/signup-process-of-shopify-store-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/signup-process-of-shopify-store-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/signup-process-of-shopify-store-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/signup-process-of-shopify-store-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Signup Process of Shopify Store-Select your type of store" width="652" height="318"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Next, you’ll get to choose what you want to create with Shopify like Create an online store or make an eCommerce store from your existing website, etc.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">And after that, you have to select the theme which you want for your store from the provided options.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">You can customize your theme from appearance/theme option then you will see customize option and from there you are able to choose themes, publish another theme, publish changes with the new theme by going to the setting option in the theme. From theme customization option you can change your brand logo which you have created from Shopify tool (Discussed above) or any other custom brand logo which you want to put into your store, customize featured products, On sale products, sliders, and many more design related things without any coding knowledge.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">After that you have to create a menu bar for your store, you will see the left sidebar an option to create pages and also include it into navigation from the setting of pages itself.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/Add-pages-in-Shopify-Store.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Add-pages-in-Shopify-Store-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Add-pages-in-Shopify-Store-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Add-pages-in-Shopify-Store-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Add-pages-in-Shopify-Store-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Add Pages in Shopify Store" width="652" height="318"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">And if you need other settings like payment gateway integration, store location, store address, etc, you will find all required settings into the left sidebar setting options.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">For the dashboard of all your analytics, you can just click on the Home or dashboard button and you will be redirected towards your dashboard.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">For adding your products to Shopify also much easier than other platforms as you can see left sidebar options, products-&gt; add a product then you can see there is an option to add title, description, product image, decide to price, add featured image of your product. And also if you need to add digital products as an attachment then you need to install a free app from Shopify app store named- <strong>download product </strong>and then after this, you can attach the downloadable product or file into the option provided at the top and just click on it and then you will be redirected to another page where you can select the file you want to sell like .zip file, images, pdf files, videos, mp3, etc.</span></p>
<h2><span style="color: #000000;">Features of Shopify</span></h2>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Sell your products everywhere</strong>: Use Shopify to sell your products to anyone and everywhere like any online marketplace with easy integration.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/Sell-your-products-everywhere.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Sell-your-products-everywhere-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Sell-your-products-everywhere-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Sell-your-products-everywhere-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Sell-your-products-everywhere-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Sell your products everywhere" width="748" height="501"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Easy do marketing of your business</strong>: Use if to do any type of marketing like sell on Facebook, Instagram, use google shopping and it also includes some built-in tools that help you to create, monitor, and analyze your campaigns.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/Easy-do-marketing-of-your-business.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Easy-do-marketing-of-your-business-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Easy-do-marketing-of-your-business-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Easy-do-marketing-of-your-business-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Easy-do-marketing-of-your-business-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Easy do marketing of your business" width="719" height="526"></figure></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Manage Everything you want</strong>: Here on Shopify, use a single dashboard to manage everything like orders, shipping, and payments.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><span style="color: #000000;"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/Manage-Everything-you-want.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Manage-Everything-you-want-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Manage-Everything-you-want-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Manage-Everything-you-want-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/31/responsive/Manage-Everything-you-want-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Manage Everything you want" width="734" height="484"></figure></span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Why Shopify Ecommerce Platform is highly recommended?</strong></span></h3>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Great Load Time</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Quick Setup</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Easy Migration</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Easy Payment Gateway Integration</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Addons</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Custom Domain</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Great Designs</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Shopify is the best and most known platform for <strong>small and midsize businesses</strong> (SMBs) and also Shopify is a high-rated solution that has everything that a merchant or seller or store owner needs to set up their online shop and even offline. Shopify also allows you to easily integrate with social media selling tools and integration with amazon also.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Shopify also has enough payment capabilities that can enable any merchant to accept credit cards directly from Shopify such that no third party accounts needed for this. With payments offer, payment details are directly synced with the orders which makes it easy to see how much you have been paid without leaving Shopify and it’s on your dashboard panel.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">Credit card rates range from 2..9% to 2.4% depending on the Plan which you have subscribed to.</span></p>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;">Official Shopify Price</span></h3>
<table style="width: 733px;" width="602">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td style="width: 282.524px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Shopify Pricing Reviews 2020</strong></span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 158.252px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Shopify Basic</strong></span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 96.1165px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Shopify</strong></span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 194.175px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Shopify Advanced</strong></span></p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 282.524px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Monthly Price</strong></span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 158.252px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;">$29</span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 96.1165px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;">$79</span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 194.175px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;">$299</span></p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 282.524px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>1 Years Price</strong></span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 158.252px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;">$26.10</span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 96.1165px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;">$71.10</span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 194.175px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;">$269.10</span></p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 282.524px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Savings (%)</strong></span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 158.252px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;">10%</span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 96.1165px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;">10%</span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 194.175px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;">10%</span></p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 282.524px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>2 Years Price</strong></span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 158.252px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;">$23.20</span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 96.1165px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;">$63.2</span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 194.175px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;">$239.20</span></p>
</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="width: 282.524px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Savings (%)</strong></span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 158.252px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;">20%</span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 96.1165px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;">20%</span></p>
</td>
<td style="width: 194.175px;">
<p><span style="color: #000000;">20%</span></p>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;">Pros of Shopify Store</span></h3>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Automatically hosted on cloud servers, don’t worry about server maintenance and downtime and also about costs.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Very easy to use and user friendly.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Great free themes available</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Very low monthly fees</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Numerous Shopify partners present for your support.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Very high engaged community on Shopify.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Many options present for third party integration from Shopify</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Multi-channel retailing is much easy.</span></li>
</ul>
<h3><span style="color: #000000;">Cons of Shopify Store</span></h3>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Additional transaction fees for external gateways</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">No free plan available</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #000000;">Limited customization</span></li>
</ul>
<h4><span style="color: #000000;"><strong>Conclusion</strong></span></h4>
<p><span style="color: #000000;">You can use Shopify easily and no coding knowledge required. Shopify allows you to build your eCommerce store with easy migration from other platforms and easy to use and setup. It’s very useful when you didn’t want to worry about your store domain, management, and server maintenance. Its 99.9% uptime from Shopify hosted eCommerce store.</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Thrive Themes Review 2020 | Pros, Cons, Features and Comparisions             </title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankit.digital/thrive-themes-review.html"/>
        <id>https://ankit.digital/thrive-themes-review.html</id>
            <category term="Reviews"/>
            <category term="Review"/>

        <updated>2020-10-07T02:08:34+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Thrive-Themes-Review.jpg" alt="" />
                    Hello guys!! Today we are going to discuss one of the best&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Thrive-Themes-Review.jpg" alt="" />
                <p class="p1">Hello guys!! Today we are going to discuss one of the best and high rated page builder plugin - <strong>Thrive Architect</strong>. Thrive themes are not just limited to Thrive Architect but it also contains few more products focused on maximizing the website's conversion rate like - Thrive Leads, Thrive Quiz Builder, Thrive Apprentice, Thrive Comments, Thrive Optimize, Thrive Ultimatum, Thrive Ovation and more. All these are bundled together and available as Thrive membership. These tools can make website conversions easier for you. It has a beautifully designed dashboard and an easier view of all their products that helps you choose your conversion goal and move ahead with it flexibly. </p>
<p class="p1">Also thrive includes beautiful conversion-focused WordPress themes which helps you to make beautiful WordPress websites with lesser hassle. </p>
<p class="p1">We are going to discuss and introduce you to all the thrive products, thrive themes, plugins, and understand their usage. </p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>About Thrive Themes</strong></span></p>
<p class="p1">Firstly we will let you know what is thrive themes? </p>
<p class="p1">Thrive Themes are advanced yet simple to use WordPress products and the package of tools. Thrive themes create conversion-optimized plugins and themes to give you a boost to your business. Thrive themes believes in providing an excellent user experience for all of their products. </p>
<p class="p1">You can easily learn more about specific features from Thrive Themes blog section. They often talk about their product-related features and their use-cases. </p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>History of Thrive Themes</strong></span></p>
<p class="p1">It was founded by marketing expert Shane Melaugh and tech fanatic Paul McCarthy in 2013.</p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>Thrive University</strong></span></p>
<p class="p1">Very lesser people know that Thrive themes also has its own virtual university. You can check about it at Thrive University on search engines they are awesome in terms of the value they provide to the end-user. They do have an amazing UI as well. </p>
<p class="p1">Do know that you can get access to 20+ different guides, video courses, and training webinar recordings in Thrive University which can help you to build your own online business. If you didn't know that, then you are not alone. Most of the internet marketers don’t know about as well. Due to this thrive themes decided to change their courses into virtual university courses and guides which is now called Thrive University. You can easily register into Thrive University for free and learn what you want. Basics are free but some are only for their paid members. But after you get Thrive membership registration you can learn maximum from it. For registration Go to thrivethemes.com/university-register. </p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1">In thrive university, you get to know about how to grow your list of leads, how to create landing pages, create a funnel, increase conversions, and also how to build a website.</p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>Plan of Thrive Membership</strong></span></p>
<p class="p1">Thrive Membership- $19/month (paid annually), Benefits- Use all thrive themes and plugins on 25 websites.</p>
<p class="p1">Agency Membership- $49/month (paid annually), Benefits- Use all thrive themes and plugins on 50 websites.</p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>After purchasing you will get :</strong></span></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Full suite of thrive themes with all plugins.</li>
<li class="li1">Updates &amp; Instant Access to New Plugins</li>
<li class="li1">Members Only Courses, Templates and Content</li>
<li class="li1">Unlimited Support</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>Integrations:</strong></span></p>
<p class="p1">Thrive themes and its products can be easily integrated into the below world’s best tools and platforms:</p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1"><strong>ActiveCampaign</strong>- Integration with ActiveCampaign email marketing</li>
<li class="li1"><strong>Amazon SES</strong>- Affordable email delivery by Amazon</li>
<li class="li1"><strong>Constant Contact</strong>- Integration with Constant Contact email marketing</li>
<li class="li1"><strong>ConvertKit</strong>- Integration with Constant Contact email marketing</li>
<li class="li1"><strong>Drip</strong>- Integration with Constant Contact email marketing</li>
<li class="li1"><strong>Facebook</strong>- Integration with facebook for developers page.</li>
<li class="li1"><strong>GetResponse</strong>- Integration with GetResponse email marketing</li>
<li class="li1"><strong>Google</strong>- Set up an API Connection with a Google Account</li>
<li class="li1"><strong>GoToWebinar</strong>- Add new registrants to GoToWebinar events</li>
<li class="li1"><strong>HubSpot</strong>- Integration with HubSpot email marketing</li>
<li class="li1"><strong>SendGrid</strong>- Integration with the SendGrid autoresponder</li>
<li class="li1"><strong>WordPress Users</strong>- Register WordPress user accounts for new leads</li>
<li class="li1"><strong>Zapier</strong>- Integration with Zapier, an online tool for connecting various apps</li>
<li class="li1"><strong>Zoom</strong>- Integration with Zapier, an online tool for connecting various apps</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>List of Thrive Products</strong></span></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Thrive Architect</li>
<li class="li1">Thrive Theme Builder</li>
<li class="li1">Thrive Leads</li>
<li class="li1">Thrive Quiz Builder</li>
<li class="li1">Thrive Ultimatum</li>
<li class="li1">Thrive Ovation</li>
<li class="li1">Thrive Optimize</li>
<li class="li1">Headline Optimizer</li>
<li class="li1">Thrive Apprentice</li>
<li class="li1">Thrive Comments</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1">Let's start with our first thrive product:</p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>Thrive Architect / Thrive Page Builder detailed review</strong></span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/thrive.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/thrive-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/thrive-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/thrive-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/thrive-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Thrive architect" width="202" height="58"></figure>
<p class="p1">Main Motive of thrive architect is to convert your ideas into the fastest converting landing pages with its visual WordPress page builder tool/Plugin. If you are working for your business then you have to use a tool that should be easy and should not consume your time and energy much and this visual page builder that is built for business and conversion focused websites. </p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Why Thrive Architect is different from others?</strong></p>
<p class="p1">Instant Drag and Drop editing</p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1"> When you open your thrive architect editor, everything will follow one simple idea. You can call it “click-to-edit”. If you need to change something, you click on it and you will see your edits instantly on your visual editor. And if you want to move something, you have to just click, drag and drop.  </li>
</ol>
<p class="p1">No coding and designing skills needed</p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1"> There is 334 designed and 100% focused for just conversion landing page templates that come built-in with Thrive Architect. It's just simply the fastest way to create professional sales pages, opt-in pages, and more, that can be published instantly and while being completely customizable.</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1">Pre-Built Elements for conversion</p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1"> You can replace a dozen plugins to thanks the conversion-focused elements by Thrive themes which is right away built into Thrive Architect, which also includes customizable buttons, testimonial templates that are already designed by the world’s best designers. It also has countdown timers and lead generation forms that are also much customizable and can be integrated with your favorite email marketing tools or any CRM app you prefer.</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><strong>What you can build with Thrive Architect?</strong></p>
<p class="p1">Thrive Architect is not just only a visual editor for Wordpress, but it’s the one that is focused more on business websites, built by entrepreneurs.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>You can create a high converting homepage</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1"> As we know our homepage is one of the most visited pages on your site. And if you don’t feel your homepage making the impression you want it to make and also if it is not engaging visitors and boosting your conversions then with Thrive Architect page builder, you can use one of the templates designed by designers and developers only for you or you can also build a beautiful and professional-looking homepage or improve the layout of your existing homepage by adding things like columns, forms, gallery, social share icons or more than these.</li>
</ol>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.02.22-AM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.02.22-AM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.02.22-AM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.02.22-AM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.02.22-AM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="" width="615" height="456"></figure>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Landing pages for your business</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Every online business requires a mailing list which should have a larger number of emails with details that’s why Thrive Themes provides more than 25 landing pages templates (along with Thrive Leads) that you can use to generate your email list with free or paid offers. Many startups start with a simple landing page to get leads and a business idea.</li>
</ol>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.02.10-AM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.02.10-AM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.02.10-AM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.02.10-AM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.02.10-AM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="" width="612" height="343"></figure>
<p class="p1"><strong>Webinar Page or Product Launch Pages</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1"> Thrive Architect includes a suitable set of pages or pre-designed templates by which you can easily build all the pages you just need to announce, get leads for, and also you can expire a live webinar event. </li>
</ol>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.01.05-AM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.01.05-AM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.01.05-AM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.01.05-AM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.01.05-AM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="" width="614" height="451"></figure>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>Some Advance Tricks into this Wordpress Page Builder:</strong></span></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Ultra-Flexible Column Layouts</li>
<li class="li1">Beautiful Text and Image Combinations</li>
<li class="li1">Get Magazine Look with total font customization</li>
<li class="li1">Full-width layouts</li>
<li class="li1">Advanced Hover Effects</li>
<li class="li1">Style All Details</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>Build Better Customer Experience for mobile visitors:</strong></span></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Preview your page on different screen sizes.</li>
<li class="li1">Toggle Visibility of Elements.</li>
<li class="li1">Check everything with Mobile responsive editing.</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Some Featured and Beautiful Blocks which you can customize easily:</strong></p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.03.40-AM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.03.40-AM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.03.40-AM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.03.40-AM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-1.03.40-AM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="" width="613" height="643"></figure>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"> <strong>Some Important Blocks with the help of that you can build awesome pages (All are customizable)</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Text</li>
<li class="li1">Heading</li>
<li class="li1">Image</li>
<li class="li1">Background Section</li>
<li class="li1">Column Layout</li>
<li class="li1">Click to tweet</li>
<li class="li1">Social Share</li>
<li class="li1">Facebook Comments</li>
<li class="li1">Custom Menu</li>
<li class="li1">Divider</li>
<li class="li1">Counter</li>
<li class="li1">Progress Bar</li>
<li class="li1">Post Grid</li>
<li class="li1">Rating</li>
<li class="li1">Tabs</li>
<li class="li1">Toggle</li>
<li class="li1">Table of Contents</li>
<li class="li1">Custom HTML/CSS</li>
<li class="li1">Google Maps</li>
<li class="li1">Wordpress content</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>Thrive Theme Builder</strong></span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"> <img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.31.31-PM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.31.31-PM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.31.31-PM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.31.31-PM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.31.31-PM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="" width="626" height="116"></figure>
<p class="p1">Thrive Theme Builder makes you build your Wordpress website with front end visual theme building. Build and edit every aspect of a Wordpress website with a drag and drop designer tool. If you go for entire membership you will also get access to conversion-focused companion theme and thrive architect light theme.</p>
<p class="p1">Thrive theme builder is a Wordpress theme builder and site builder and also free from the traditional Wordpress framework to give you control over your entire site and its parts. </p>
<p class="p1">Thrive theme builder allows you to visually create and customize your footer, header and blog templates with sidebar, layout, category pages, search pages, 404 pages and more than you think it will be.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Special Features of Thrive Theme Builder:</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Launch your website within 15-20 minutes only.</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Starting a new website with a wordpress theme and then customizing it is hard. But here comes Thrive theme builder for your rescue. It customizes the theme and makes it lightweight with faster loading speed. Thrive theme builder comes with a site set-up wizard that will hold your hand through a series of steps to make your website live within 15-20 minutes only.</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><strong>Brand update everywhere in seconds.</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1"> Thrive Theme Builder helps you to manage your brand everywhere from one location with global color settings, font management and effortless control over your brand logo. You can quickly change brand elements everywhere with single click or every pixel to your needs in easy manner.</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><strong>Design your professional theme by thinking of conversion in your mind.</strong></p>
<p class="p1"> A website build with thrive theme builder can help you to grow your business and get more email subscribers.<strong> </strong></p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Mobile Responsive</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1"> You can build your website with mobile responsiveness like you can use responsive elements for this and all responsive elements are inbuilt with thrive theme builder plugin.</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><strong>It can be integrated with your favorite tools</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1"> We all know that integrating with online tools are quite harder but with thrive theme builder it's not that difficult. Thrive theme builder is integrated with better business tools that are highly in use by the various businesses including email marketing systems, webinar platforms, Zapier, and more tools for your use.</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1">Do you know how many people or website owners are currently using Thrive theme builder? No. Its 13097 peoples.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.31.58-PM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.31.58-PM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.31.58-PM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.31.58-PM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.31.58-PM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="" width="799" height="321"> </figure>
<p class="p1">As we all know if any website’s home page loads quickly then it has good chances to get conversions. People tend to visit the sites that loads faster. With thrive theme builder you will get a conversion-focused homepage with quick loading speed.</p>
<p class="p1">And your homepage needs to hold an entire load of your complete brand. And also it’s the first thing your potential customers will see and maybe the last if your loading speed is poor. Here in thrive theme builder you will also get inbuilt theme companion named as shapeshift which comes with five pre-designed homepages with conversion in mind taken. Each homepage is pre-designed for high speed and outlined by industry experts to fit the needs of a specific business, plus allows you to do your customizations. If you think you can design better then you are free to create or customize your homepage by using page blocks.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>With Thrive Theme Builder you don’t need:</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">CSS Styling Plugins</li>
<li class="li1">Custom Sidebar Plugins</li>
<li class="li1">Contact Form Plugins</li>
<li class="li1">Related Post Plugins</li>
<li class="li1">Category Redirect Plugin</li>
<li class="li1">Page &amp; Post Cloning Plugins</li>
<li class="li1">Author Box Plugins</li>
<li class="li1">Custom 404 Page Plugins</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Top Features of Thrive Theme Builder:</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Coming Soon Page will be woo-commerce compatible</li>
<li class="li1">Easily generate leads with your footer sales form.</li>
<li class="li1">Easily turn your 404 pages into a custom landing page and convert 404 pages into traffic, sales, and leads.</li>
<li class="li1">Control your sidebars with front end builder.</li>
<li class="li1">Customize your headers easily.</li>
<li class="li1">Build and customize your menu bar with custom menu and change its layout.</li>
<li class="li1">Create custom search pages with a well-designed structure.</li>
<li class="li1">Build your post blocks with beautiful list-builder skins within the Thrive theme builder.</li>
<li class="li1">Get a pre-designed author box and use it for your blog posts.</li>
<li class="li1">Convert your visitors into leads with various lead generation elements.</li>
<li class="li1">Build beautiful testimonial for your website with testimonials elements and templates.</li>
<li class="li1">Get various templates, content blocks, and designs.</li>
<li class="li1">Manage Fonts in a location.</li>
<li class="li1">Use built-in fonts, icons gradients, and dividers.</li>
<li class="li1">Create Styled Custom fields for everything.</li>
<li class="li1">Site Speed Optimization Dashboard.</li>
<li class="li1">Easily update your site’s global color with smart colors.</li>
<li class="li1">Every element and template are mobile-friendly.</li>
<li class="li1">Includes shapeshift which is alone theme companion.</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>Thrive Leads</strong></span></p>
<p class="p1">Thrive Leads is the product of thrive themes and with the help of this, you can build your email list faster than ever.</p>
<p class="p1">With Thrive Leads you can increase your conversion for almost 200%. Thrive leads is the list building solution that is created by a team of people who are experts in conversion optimization. </p>
<p class="p1">Using thrive leads is like having your list building and conversion right into a powerful piece. This is no told list building plugin. </p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Why Thrive Leads are different?</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Design and Deploy</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1"> Thrive Leads combines every type of form you need in one single plugin and it gives you a drag and drop editor to create a perfect design every time when you are going to design anything.</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><strong>Advanced Targeting</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1"> Boost your conversion by showing targeted, offers based on your posts, categories, tags, and more.</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><strong>A/B Testing</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1"> Thrive leads comes with advanced but easy to use the testing feature. This can increase your conversions and with the use of this plugin you can do A/B testing with your lead gen campaigns. </li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><strong>Actionable Reporting &amp; Insights</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1"> Thrive Leads gives you an overview of the important metrics like - various opt-in forms and their performance over time, and the source of traffic on those forms.</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1">Below is the list of versatile features that makes Thrive Leads a no brainer tool for optimized lead generation. </p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Thrive Box (Popup Lightbox)</strong></p>
<p class="p1">A popup which can be added to your content and helps in grabbing the attention.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Sticky Ribbon</strong></p>
<p class="p1">Add a ribbon type form that can be placed on the top of your content. It helps grab visitor attention as it remains sticky even during the scroll. It also provides an option to the visitor to close it.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>In-Line Form</strong></p>
<p class="p1">You can use opt-in form anywhere over the content where you want to add by using shortcodes.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Slide-in</strong></p>
<p class="p1">You can add slide form which slides into view from the corner which is almost equally attention-grabbing.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Opt-in Widget</strong></p>
<p class="p1">You can easily add a sidebar opt-in widget to grab attention to the visitor while they are reading your content. They can easily look into your sidebar content and thus have higher chances of conversions.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Screen Overlay</strong></p>
<p class="p1">You can add screen overlay contact form, email opt-in form which can cover your overall screen to grab the attention of your offers to the visitors coming to your website.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Content Lock</strong></p>
<p class="p1">You can also add a lock or unlock opt-in form and thus you can offer your visitor a reward and get conversion easily.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Yes/No and Multiple choice Forms</strong></p>
<p class="p1">You can also add multiple choice opt-in form in which you can add yes or no option to the form and with this you can get genuine leads for your website.</p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Features of Thrive Leads:</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">All opt-in forms type at your fingertips.</li>
<li class="li1">Grow your list with A/B Testing.</li>
<li class="li1">Boost your conversions with Smartlinks &amp; Smartexits.</li>
<li class="li1">Pre-designed templates</li>
<li class="li1">Discover detailed and advanced stats and report.</li>
</ol>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"> <img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.32.11-PM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.32.11-PM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.32.11-PM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.32.11-PM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.32.11-PM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="" width="729" height="360"></figure>
<p class="p1"><strong>There are three level of customization:</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Show or hide certain opt-in form types</li>
<li class="li1">Show or hide certain elements on the opt-in form</li>
<li class="li1">Tweak any detail with mobile responsive editing</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><strong>Easy to integrate with your email marketing service:</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Amazon SES</li>
<li class="li1">Google</li>
<li class="li1">Hubspot</li>
<li class="li1">Facebook</li>
<li class="li1">Drip</li>
<li class="li1">Mailrelay</li>
<li class="li1">Sandlane</li>
<li class="li1">Mailchimp</li>
<li class="li1">Mailgun</li>
<li class="li1">Sendy</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1">Thrive Leads has direct integration for the popular email services. Also you can use it with any system that creates an HTML signup form, opening thrive leads up to hundreds of integrations.</p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>Thrive Quiz Builder</strong></span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.58.18-PM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.58.18-PM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.58.18-PM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.58.18-PM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.58.18-PM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="" width="613" height="202"></figure>
<p>With the help of Thrive Quiz Builder, you can create or design beautiful quizzes for your business to increase your conversion rate by entertaining your visitors. We all know quizzes are not only for fun but it can increase your visitor engagement and revenue or conversion rate with almost 50% as you can’t think about that. Not only this, but it also lowers your bounce rate thus giving a good boost to user retention. </p>
<p class="p1">You can create stunning Quizzes in seconds which could be time-consuming otherwise. </p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"> <img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.58.31-PM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.58.31-PM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.58.31-PM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.58.31-PM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.58.31-PM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="" width="617" height="386"></figure>
<p class="p1"><strong>Build Complex Quizzes without Coding:</strong></p>
<p class="p1">Thrive Quiz Builder gives you the ability to create complex quizzes and it also makes it extremely easy to visualize what you want to build in your quiz and how it flows in our quiz builder.</p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Easily see all the questions and answers flows so that you can look at what you want to build is correct or not.</li>
<li class="li1">You can build a branching quiz from which you can ask any question about the previous answer.</li>
<li class="li1">Choose between image and text questions.</li>
</ol>
<figure class="post__image"> <img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.58.45-PM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.58.45-PM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.58.45-PM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.58.45-PM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-16-at-3.58.45-PM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="" width="616" height="452"></figure>
<p class="p1"><strong>What things offered by Thrive Quiz Builder??</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Quiz Types:</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Display the final result of the Quiz as a number.</li>
<li class="li1">Display the final result of the Quiz as a Percentage.</li>
<li class="li1">Display final result of Quiz as a category</li>
<li class="li1">Display the final result of the Quiz as per the number of the correct answers given.</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><strong>Analytics:</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Across Time Tracking</li>
<li class="li1">Start vs. Finishing</li>
<li class="li1">Quiz Flow</li>
<li class="li1">Individual Question Stats</li>
<li class="li1">Social Sharing Stats</li>
<li class="li1">User Stats.</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><strong>Quiz Templates:</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Build from scratch</li>
<li class="li1">List Building</li>
<li class="li1">Social Shares</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><strong>Easy Quiz Builder</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Overview Navigation</li>
<li class="li1">Complex Logic</li>
<li class="li1">Quiz Flow</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>Thrive Ultimatum</strong></span></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--full align-center"> <img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-4.59.17-PM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-4.59.17-PM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-4.59.17-PM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-4.59.17-PM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-4.59.17-PM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Thrive Ultimatum " width="475" height="107"></figure>
<p class="p1">Thrive ultimatum is the ultimate marketing tool for Wordpress. Thrive Ultimatum can help you to take advantage of every aspect of scarcity marketing.</p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Easy Fixed Date Campaigns.</li>
<li class="li1">Automatically recurring campaigns.</li>
<li class="li1">The evergreen systems</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1">Thrive ultimatum comes with professionally designed templates for countdown timers, widgets, and floating banners. With each template, you can make stylish and conversion-focused widgets.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.01.07-PM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.01.07-PM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.01.07-PM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.01.07-PM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.01.07-PM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Thrive Ultimatum2" width="447" height="396"> </figure>
<p class="p1"><strong>Boost your sales by showing the right offer to the customers:</strong></p>
<p class="p1">With thrive ultimatum, you can easily advertise your special offers all across your website. You can easily show countdown timers in the widget area or banners to convert more visitors towards your special offers. </p>
<p class="p1">Or if you want to show only the countdowns on specific pages, in blog posts on a specific category.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>How you can use Thrive Ultimatum on your website?</strong></p>
<ul class="ul1">
<li class="li1">Increase product sales with a special offer.</li>
<li class="li1">Create a product launch</li>
<li class="li1">Boost your e-commerce sales</li>
<li class="li1">Earn More commission as an affiliate</li>
</ul>
<p class="p1">Features:</p>
<ul class="ul1">
<li class="li1">Multi-Page Campaigns</li>
<li class="li1">Auto-Pilot</li>
<li class="li1">Unlimited Campaigns</li>
<li class="li1">Floating Footer Bar</li>
<li class="li1">Countdown Widgets</li>
<li class="li1">Floating Header Bar</li>
<li class="li1">Time Zones Supported</li>
<li class="li1">Dynamic Updates</li>
<li class="li1">Design Templates</li>
<li class="li1">Display Anywhere</li>
<li class="li1">Fully Mobile Friendly</li>
<li class="li1">Auto-End Campaign</li>
<li class="li1">Dynamic Redirect Links</li>
<li class="li1">Lockdown Features</li>
</ul>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>Thrive Ovation</strong></span></p>
<p class="p1">With the help of thrive ovation, you can easily and beautifully design testimonials and reviews which are given by your customer for your services and good response and you can feature all of them on your website with the help of this plugin.</p>
<p class="p1">You don’t need to use another plugin for just setup for all of your testimonials of the website by your customers and you will forget about these once you use this plugin.</p>
<p class="p1">This testimonials plugin is the easiest way to start taking advantage of one of the most beautiful conversion boosters. </p>
<p class="p1">When you are going to publish your sales page, you should need to add some of your testimonials which defines that how much your services are liked by the customers or your visitors so that new visitors can be converted easily.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"> <img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.02.43-PM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.02.43-PM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.02.43-PM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.02.43-PM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.02.43-PM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="ThriveOvation " width="477" height="282"></figure>
<p class="p1"><strong>Features of Thrive Ovation:</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Transform your Wordpress comments into testimonials</li>
<li class="li1">Import your testimonials or reviews from social media easily.</li>
<li class="li1">Easily collect testimonials by dedicated landing pages automatically.</li>
<li class="li1">Save your time with testimonials management.</li>
<li class="li1">Display beautiful testimonials.</li>
<li class="li1">Update testimonials dynamically</li>
<li class="li1">Professionally designed templates available.</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>Thrive Optimize</strong></span></p>
<p class="p1">Optimize your landing page with A/B Testing with the help of Thrive Optimize. Launch you’re A/B testing faster and cheap with thrive optimize. </p>
<p class="p1">With the help of this Split testing addon in Thrive Architect you can test your 2 landing page with different designs but on the same topic, you can do easy and fast A/B Testing for both landing pages to test which gives better performance.</p>
<p class="p1">Thrive Optimize is a very simple and fast A/B testing addon for Thrive Architect that gives you the power to run highly-effective split tests for the landing pages.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"> <img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.04.21-PM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.04.21-PM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.04.21-PM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.04.21-PM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.04.21-PM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="ThriveOptimise" width="516" height="331"></figure>
<p class="p1"><strong>Steps to do split tests:</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Create a page.</li>
<li class="li1">Create a variation of that page</li>
<li class="li1">Pick a conversion goal.</li>
<li class="li1">Start the test.</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><strong>Features of Thrive Optimize:</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Fast A/B Testing</li>
<li class="li1">Unlimited Tests</li>
<li class="li1">Unlimited Test Variations</li>
<li class="li1">3 Conversion Goals</li>
<li class="li1">Custom Traffic Distribution</li>
<li class="li1">Detailed Reporting</li>
<li class="li1">Automatic Winner Feature</li>
<li class="li1">100% Visual Editing</li>
<li class="li1">100% WordPress</li>
<li class="li1">One-Click Cloning</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1">For more information regarding Thrive Optimize, you can get from official websites of Thrive Themes.</p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>Headline Optimizer</strong></span></p>
<p class="p1">With the help of Headline Optimizer, you can optimize your headlines with the help of various fonts available on Wordpress or Thrive itself. Also, you can design your headlines with awesome templates and creatives. Also with the help of Thrive Headline Optimizer, you can build and design your headlines with faster and beautiful customization easily.</p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>Thrive Comments</strong></span></p>
<p class="p1">Design and build your comment section below your blog posts with the help of Thrive Comments plugin for Wordpress. Build engagement like Reddit and Facebook comments section with the help of thrive comments. </p>
<p class="p1">The thrive comments include the most addictive elements of social media and added them to your Wordpress comments. </p>
<p class="p1">You can build an engaging community by giving:</p>
<ul class="ul1">
<li class="li1">Like features of the visitor’s comment.</li>
<li class="li1">Achievement through unlocking various badges.</li>
<li class="li1">Validation through featured comments.</li>
<li class="li1">An option to get a comment shared on social media in just 1 click.</li>
</ul>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Convert your comments into conversions:</strong></p>
<p class="p1">As website owners, most of the time and effort goes towards only in trying to get visitors to interact with their site like click this button, visit this page, subscribe us, sign up etc. But if any visitor takes time to give their reviews on your website then this can help you to collect your visitor's comments and email address which you can ask before leaving comments by your visitors.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Some features of Thrive Comments:</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Conversion Focused Comments</li>
<li class="li1">Addictive Encouragement</li>
<li class="li1">Access to Unspoken Opinions</li>
<li class="li1">One-Click Delegation</li>
<li class="li1">Automatic Resource Links</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><strong>What will you get with thrive comments?</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Assign Users Badges</li>
<li class="li1">Up-Vote &amp; Down-Vote</li>
<li class="li1">Display Featured Comments</li>
<li class="li1">Comment Boosting Design</li>
<li class="li1">Post From Social Accounts</li>
<li class="li1">Social Sharing</li>
<li class="li1">Subscribe to a Post's Comments</li>
<li class="li1">Auto Generate Visitor Information</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1"><strong>Conversion Focused Comments</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Choose What Happens After A Comment</li>
<li class="li1">Different C.T.A. for First Time Commenters</li>
<li class="li1">Lazy Load for Speed Optimization</li>
<li class="li1">Audience Insights</li>
</ol>
<p class="p3"><strong>Comment Moderation &amp; Management</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">No Click Comment Sorting</li>
<li class="li1">Filter comments based on many things.</li>
<li class="li1">Delegate Comments</li>
<li class="li1">Auto-Link Keywords</li>
</ol>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"> <img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.05.19-PM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.05.19-PM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.05.19-PM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.05.19-PM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.05.19-PM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="ThriveComments" width="478" height="250"></figure>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><strong>Thrive Apprentice</strong></span></p>
<p class="p1">With Thrive Apprentice, you can get everything you need to make your online course more professional and efficient. You can build your online course and with the help of Thrive Apprentice various elements.</p>
<p class="p1">We all know that creating professional online courses are more expensive and time-consuming. The experience should be more like assembling and quick to set up thereby leaving your guests impressed with the results.</p>
<p class="p1">And for you, thrive apprentice course creation experience is very simple. You just need to follow steps of the setup process to create online course lessons, chapters, and modules with the fast design power.</p>
<p class="p1">For your students, subscribers, and upcoming customers, thrive apprentice learning environment is easy and helpful to use and learn with visually engaging professional courses.</p>
<p class="p1">In thrive apprentice, you can use any type of combinations like texts, images, videos, and design elements to teach and provide learnings to your customers and students. </p>
<p class="p1">With the power of limitless page building plugin thrive architect which is the most advanced drag and drop page builder plugin or visual editor for Wordpress and you can craft each lesson for your course. For clarity and ease, you can use any combination like text and images elements to teach the entire course.</p>
<p class="p1">Thrive Apprentice includes important teaching tools like tables, column layouts, lists, or multiple formats to get your points. With Thrive Apprentice, create a learning experience for your students and customers with an easy course creation process for yourself directly from your website.</p>
<p class="p1">Due to the lack of a professional touch may cause people to walk away from your website which you are willing to provide courses on it without giving a chance on your content. And this reaction from the visitor will reflect poorly on your authority on making profitable sales and in the future its more difficult to achieve the expertise on your business.</p>
<p class="p1">You should remember that you need to ask people for their time, money, and contact information in exchange for an online learning course so they must remember you for all the correct reasons.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>You can even grow your course organically.</strong></p>
<p class="p1">Thrive Apprentice has the power to make both types of courses like If you need to create a simple course with just a few lessons to serve as your mailing list or want to create an advanced course to sell as a premium product.</p>
<p class="p1">Thrive Apprentice gives you the flexibility to create video course than others as LMS have also had that features but are paid and much complex to use and in Thrive Apprentice, you can build and launch text courses and also one-page simple guides. You can also choose to sell a single course or create a range of all your courses that are available for your paying members and all can be managed by a single dashboard which is user friendly with a good User interface.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"> <img loading="lazy"  src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.06.08-PM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.06.08-PM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.06.08-PM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.06.08-PM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/29/responsive/Screenshot-2020-07-24-at-5.06.08-PM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="ThriveApprentice" width="500" height="274"></figure>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1">You can start by creating a simple course and then launch it. You can add more lessons after launching your course over time to increase the value of your course. Thrive Apprentice can be your back on every step of your way in launching awesome courses and online learnings for your students, customers.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Benefits in Building online courses with Thrive Apprentice:</strong></p>
<ul class="ul1">
<li class="li1">Create an Online Course with the feel of a professional designer.</li>
<li class="li1">Add text linked navigation for the next course.</li>
<li class="li1">Fast Launch of your online course without wasting your time.</li>
<li class="li1">Build many courses as you want because it is limitless.</li>
<li class="li1">Fast and simple integration with <strong>sendowl</strong> to run your courses on premium membership products.</li>
<li class="li1">Easily grow your email list by offering new customers a free course.</li>
<li class="li1">Add beautiful user experience on a new user registration panel.</li>
<li class="li1">Restrict access to non-subscribers to prevent your course from spamming or thieving.</li>
<li class="li1">Use thrive apprentice sidebars to give easy and quick navigation to your courses for your customers and students.</li>
<li class="li1">Thrive apprentice will work with any Wordpress theme.</li>
</ul>
<p class="p1"><strong>Three Primary and easy ways to grow your online course using Thrive Apprentice:</strong></p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Paid Course Strategy: Thrive Apprentice + SendOwl Deep Integration.</li>
<li class="li1">Paid Course Strategy: Thrive Apprentice + Membership Plugin</li>
<li class="li1">Free Course Strategy: Online Course Lead Magnets</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1">For more information log on to the official website: thrivethemes.com.</p>
<p class="p1">Also, for more such type of blog posts, keep visiting.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Sendy Review 2020 - Detailed Guide to Comparison and Alternatives in Email Marketing Industry</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankit.digital/sendy-review.html"/>
        <id>https://ankit.digital/sendy-review.html</id>
            <category term="Reviews"/>
            <category term="Review"/>

        <updated>2020-10-07T02:08:34+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/28/MicrosoftTeams-image-1.png" alt="Sendy reviwed honestly" />
                    You want to take control of your email marketing activities and yet&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/28/MicrosoftTeams-image-1.png" alt="Sendy reviwed honestly" />
                <p class="p1">You want to take control of your email marketing activities and yet make it do like a boss with super awesome results, well you are at the right place, keep reading the post.</p>
<p class="p2 msg msg--info">Before I start to Review <strong><a href="https://blog.ankit.digital/recommends/sendy" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Sendy</a></strong>, I'll start with the basic background. I am doing email marketing for years and I have almost used all the top notch apps available in the market be it Mailchimp, Getresponse, Sendgrid, Mailgun, and many others. But there’s very strong feeling in you when you take control of your email marketing. On my hunt for perfect email marketing solution I got to know about Amazon SES. It’s part of AWS. With Amazon SES, you can widely operate not only for email marketing but also for various for marketing automation, triggering various kind of rules for emails and much more. Plus point of having this control is that you can do many things in cost efficient manner. With Amazon SES, your cost for sending 1000 emails is just $0.10.</p>
<p class="p2"> </p>
<p class="p1">Upside of using Amazon SES is just not being a cost efficient solution but also higher inbox delivery rates (Comm’on, we are talking about Amazon Servers). You can use SES to build your email marketing process the way you want. To do that, you need to either code your own application or fins some reliable hosted app that can act as your email client.</p>
<p class="p1">Now, this is where sendy comes in. You simply need to integrate Sendy with your Amazon SES account and then you are done. Post this, you will be able to setup email list creation for various of your sites, Subscription settings, create auto responders, Optin and Double Optin emails, and more.</p>
<h3><a href="https://blog.ankit.digital/recommends/sendy" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Sendy - Email Marketing Tool</a> : Detailed Review with Pros and Cons</h3>
<p class="p1">As clear from my post, you might be of this opinion that this guy is just talking of the positive aspect only and thus you are somehow missing our review of Sendy. My friend, that’s not the case. I am here to totally justify the purpose of your visit. Till now, I just made you aware of <strong>What is Sendy? </strong>Read further to know all the pros and cons of Sendy.</p>
<p class="p2 msg msg--highlight ">Here's the link to Sendy's official Website --&gt; <a href="https://blog.ankit.digital/recommends/sendy" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Sendy - Send newsletters, 100x cheaper </a></p>
<h3 class="p1">Pros of using Sendy :</h3>
<ul class="ul1">
<li class="li1">Best part, Just one time cost of $29. No renewal fee, nothing. Be worry free for life.</li>
<li class="li1">Super flexible solution, hosted on your own server and thus you retain your data without sharing them with any Email service provider.</li>
<li class="li1">You can automate the list building and subscription settings. That is, Once the setup is correctly done, you need to to touch it again, it will do the magic based on your defined settings.</li>
<li class="li1">Setup Autoresponders and drip email series to automate your email marketing.</li>
<li class="li1">Create Email Subscription Box to place on your site and populate your email list on it’s own.</li>
<li class="li1">You can not inly use Sendy for your own, but you can make some money by selling to further to your clients. It has the option to create Sub accounts and pre-define pricing options based on Number of emails or subscribers. There by giving you can option to sell Email marketing as an option.</li>
<li class="li1">Sendy also gives multiple integration with Zapier’s connectivity. You can integrate to any possible app of your choice. For example, as soon as the person subscribe and entered to your email list, can directly be sent to your CRM as well.</li>
</ul>
<p class="p2"> </p>
<h3 class="p1">Cons of Using Sendy</h3>
<ul class="ul1">
<li class="li1">Setting up Sendy can be the pain in your ass if you not a bit techie.</li>
<li class="li1">There might be some bugs due to server’s compatibility or so. You will need those to be resolved. Though, not a big thing but can take time for a newbie.</li>
<li class="li1">Advanced email marketing automation features like behavioural tagging, drip action based on if/else<span class="Apple-converted-space">  </span>are not available.</li>
</ul>
<p class="p2"> </p>
<p class="p1">Now that I have told you all the Pros and Cons, I leave it to you to either use it or not. My post should be used as an analysis on what are the actual features you look for in an email marketing app. If the one that you need covers all of what Sendy offers, you must definitely go for it considering the cost of the system.</p>
<p class="p2"> </p>
<p class="p1">Going ahead, let me explain how to play with the system. I’ll share the important functionalities of the Sendy so that you can analyse if it fit’s in your use-cases.</p>
<p class="p2"> </p>
<ol class="ol1">
<li class="li1">Prepare your email list : If you want people To subscribe to your email list, just create a new list on your sendy setup and place the given embed code to your blog. I have attached the two screenshots to do the process.
<figure class="post__image post__image" ><img loading="lazy" src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/28/Screenshot-2020-06-14-at-1.21.42-AM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/28/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-14-at-1.21.42-AM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/28/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-14-at-1.21.42-AM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/28/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-14-at-1.21.42-AM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/28/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-14-at-1.21.42-AM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Sendy Subscriber Settings" width="1920" height="912">
<figcaption >Creating New email list with Sendy</figcaption>
</figure>
<figure class="post__image post__image" ><img loading="lazy" src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/28/Screenshot-2020-06-14-at-1.45.28-AM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/28/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-14-at-1.45.28-AM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/28/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-14-at-1.45.28-AM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/28/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-14-at-1.45.28-AM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/28/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-14-at-1.45.28-AM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Subscribe form in Sendy" width="1920" height="526">
<figcaption >Subscribe form in Sendy</figcaption>
</figure>
</li>
<li class="li1">Launch your campaigns and see detailed stats including, who open your emails, who clicked links inside your email. Mails that got bounced and people who unsubscribed will automatically be taken care with the help of the system. Next time when you send a campaign, these mail id’s would automatically be left out.
<figure class="post__image post__image--center" ><img loading="lazy" src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/28/Screenshot-2020-06-14-at-1.50.04-AM.png" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" srcset="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/28/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-14-at-1.50.04-AM-xs.png 300w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/28/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-14-at-1.50.04-AM-sm.png 480w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/28/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-14-at-1.50.04-AM-md.png 768w ,https://ankit.digital/media/posts/28/responsive/Screenshot-2020-06-14-at-1.50.04-AM-lg.png 1024w"  alt="Sendy detailed stats for an email campaign" width="1920" height="782">
<figcaption >
<p>Sendy detailed stats for an email campaign</p>
</figcaption>
</figure>
</li>
<li class="li1">Drip Series - Though this is not a proper if/else drip campaign functionality. But you can prepare your series of email for a particular set of subscribers. For example - You have launched your advertising campaigns to prepare an email list<span class="Apple-converted-space">  </span>for people who wants to learn Blogging. As part of campaign you have asked your audience that they will receive 7 lessons for 7 days (1 lesson a day). So as soon as the person as subscribed, they will be able to receive a pre defined email as the course lesson everyday. You can design your own series of emails by Clicking on Autoresponder Tab inside your selected list. </li>
<li class="li1">Launch your email marketing agency : You can create sub-accounts with proper brand name and allot credits / limits to the sub accounts to send emails. This way, you can earn easy money selling out your email marketing services.</li>
</ol>
<p class="p2"> </p>
<p class="p1">Conclusion / Takeaway - Given the price of Sendy, it is a versatile piece of software to handle your email marketing needs. This gives your the power to control your emails and the budget you spend on emails. I would rate sendy 5/5.</p>
<p class="p2 msg msg--success">If this all makes sense to you and you are interested to go for sendy, here you go - <strong><a href="https://blog.ankit.digital/recommends/sendy" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Sendy's Official Website</a></strong></p>
<p class="p1">In case you need help to configure Sendy to your hosting and do all the required setup, you can schedule a call for Sendy Setup Services.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Important tools and free resources for Student Entrepreneurs</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankit.digital/free-tools-for-student-entrepreneurs.html"/>
        <id>https://ankit.digital/free-tools-for-student-entrepreneurs.html</id>

        <updated>2020-10-07T02:08:34+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/26/Screenshot-2020-05-31-at-1.23.37-PM.png" alt="" />
                    Student entrepreneurs always look for support and new technologies to support their&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://ankit.digital/media/posts/26/Screenshot-2020-05-31-at-1.23.37-PM.png" alt="" />
                <p>Student entrepreneurs always look for support and new technologies to support their startup ideas. Many corporates and big players comes forward time to time to give back to the society and help these students in their career's journey</p>
<p class="p2"> </p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s2">Important Free Tools for Student Entrepreneurs -</span></p>
<ul class="ul1">
<li class="li1"><a href="https://bit.ly/2TSeW5W"><span class="s3">Microsoft Team</span></a> : It helps your team remain connected seamlessly. Though was a paid service earlier. Microsoft has decided to give it for free due to Covid-19 impacts on startups.</li>
<li class="li1"><a href="https://bit.ly/2ZTx7vW"><span class="s3">Github Student Pack</span> </a>: This is an awesome combo of free tools and services to help students explore some top notch services for free. Few important ones are - Free domain name from <a href="http://name.com"><span class="s4">name.com</span></a>, free hosting from DO, $100 credits from AWS, free $100 credits from Azure, Canva’s 12 months pro plan for free, Email Marketing from Sendgrid with 15000 emails per month for free, Stripe Payment Gateway free for first $1000 and more. All these benefits are more than enough for any student to kickstart their entrepreneurship journey.</li>
<li class="li1"><a href="http://FS6.com"><span class="s4">FS6.com</span></a> : This is called the Founders Hub. Different people are connected on this platform for different reasons. Some for gaining more connections, Some for finding relevant customers/ beta testers for their products, some for gaining traction and exposure for their products. Big players often list their products / SAAS for free here to give back to the community. You can find free trials of various useful tools and services on this platform.</li>
<li class="li1"><a href="https://www.shopify.in/free-trial"><span class="s4">Shopify 90 Days free Trial </span></a>- If you wish to launch your e-commerce store or want to test out some e-commerce venture without paying much, this is going to be a wonderful deal.</li>
<li class="li1"><a href="https://www.loom.com/blog/coronavirus-response"><span class="s4">Loom </span></a>: Free video recording and sharing service for teachers and students at K-12 schools, universities and educational institutions. They have also removed the recording limit on free plans and have cut the price for Loom Pro in half. They have done so in response to Covid-19 Combat.</li>
<li class="li1"><a href="https://beefree.io/index.aspx"><span class="s4">Beefree</span></a> : Helps design beautiful and responsive email templates</li>
<li class="li1"><a href="https://artofemails.com"><span class="s3">ArtofEmails</span></a> : This helps you formulate your cold email out reach templates and followup series.</li>
<li class="li1"><a href="https://zoho.com"><span class="s4">Zoho</span></a>: It is a complete suite of tools for Online office connectivity. They provide custom email address, CRM, Documents editors and a lot. Their free plan can get you started for upto 10 users without any charge.</li>
<li class="li1"><a href="https://hubspot.com"><span class="s3">Hubspot</span> </a>: It is an amazing CRM. You can use to maintain your prospects here along with minute details. It helps in followup, Lead scoring, Leads management. They provide Lifetime free plan for their CRM.</li>
<li class="li1"><a href="https://blog.calendly.com/meeting-integration-update/"><span class="s4">Calendly</span></a> : Allow people to schedule meeting with you. It has integration with top Video Conferencing softwares and calendars. People can click on the link, choose an available time slot and fix meeting with you.</li>
<li class="li1"><a href="https://hootsuite.com/pages/stay-connected"><span class="s4">Hootsuite</span></a> : Free access for Hootsuite Professional to small businesses and nonprofits until July 1st, 2020. Helping to manage social media, and stay connected with your customers and communities.</li>
</ul>
<p>I hope this list of tools and services will help you kickstart your journey to entrepreneurship. </p>
<p class="p2">Gaining Skills is much important. And nothing can be better in terms of learning than doing an internship. A good internshio give you a glimpse of how businesses works, how do people deal in corporates and at the same time you gain the skillset. Basis the same learning, you can start applying for Jobs or finding some freelance gigs on internet. </p>
<p class="p1">Finding Good Internship Opportunities</p>
<ul class="ul1">
<li class="li3"><span class="s1"><a href="https://www.internships.com/"><span class="s2">https://www.internships.com/</span></a></span></li>
<li class="li3"><span class="s1"><span class="s2"><a href="https://www.letsintern.com/">https://www.letsintern.com/</a><a href="https://www.letsintern.com/"></a></span></span></li>
</ul>
<p>I hope you like this article. Stay tuned for more valuable tips and tricks in future.</p>
<p class="p2"> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
