<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Ankit.Digital</title>
    <link href="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital" />
    <updated>2020-05-24T20:42:16+05:30</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Covid 19 Live Tracker France</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/covid-19-live-tracker-france.html"/>
        <id>https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/covid-19-live-tracker-france.html</id>

        <updated>2020-05-24T18:57:53+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    [covid19-country-updates country=FR country_list=0 layout=3 label="France Covid19 Data" colors="#d80027,#0052b4"] &nbsp; [covid19-country-updates country=France country_list=0&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>[covid19-country-updates country=FR country_list=0 layout=3 label="France Covid19 Data" colors="#d80027,#0052b4"]</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>[covid19-country-updates country=France country_list=0 layout=3 label="France Covid19 Data" colors="#d80027,#0052b4"]</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Covid 19 Tracker</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/covid-19-tracker.html"/>
        <id>https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/covid-19-tracker.html</id>

        <updated>2020-05-24T18:57:53+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    [ce_corona] &nbsp;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>[ce_corona]</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Best email marketing alternatives to Mailchimp</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/best-email-marketing-alternatives-to-mailchimp.html"/>
        <id>https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/best-email-marketing-alternatives-to-mailchimp.html</id>
            <category term="Quick Notes"/>
            <category term="Email Marketing"/>

        <updated>2020-05-24T18:57:53+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    To be honest, Mailchimp is one of the versatile email marketing platforms.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>To be honest, Mailchimp is one of the versatile email marketing platforms. But different people like to use different platforms for different use-cases. I am listing the best email marketing alternatives to Mailchimp.</p>
<ol>
<li><a href="https://ankit.digital/recommends/sendy">Sendy</a> - I have been using Sendy for around 2016. This is perfect if you already have a pre verified and double opt-in email list. I recommend you using this specially for sending newsletters. Sendy is a standalone app which can work with almost any smtp servers. Most recommend way of using sendy is to integrate it with <a href="https://www.editsoftdigital.com/amazon-ses-review/">Amazon SES</a>. It just costs $0.0001 per email sent. I see 90% inbox rate with detailed analytics of how my subscribers are performing.</li>
<li><a href="https://ankit.digital/recommends/sendfox">Sendfox</a> - Sendfox is a versatile app from Appsumo house. They don't sell it as SAAS for now. They sell it as a Lifetime Deal. You can outreach highly filtered email list through Sendfox. They have good inbox rate.</li>
<li><a href="https://ankit.digital/recommends/getgist">Getgist</a> - It is an email marketing automation platform. You can highly customise your email campaigns basis your subscriber behaviour on your already sent email, or on your website, landing page, etc. More than email marketing, they offer lead management, chatbot sequences, etc. They have their free tier program available. You can try it out.</li>
<li><a href="http://sendgrid.com">Sendgrid</a> - I have used Sendgrid for one of my client. And it worked like a charm. They have 90% + inbox rate.</li>
</ol>
<p>I hope this list helps you decide which Mailchimp alternative you would like to go with. If you know more such email marketing platform that are good alternatives of Mailchimp and aren't listed here in this post, do let me know in comments.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>5 Landing Page Builders</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/5-landing-page-builders.html"/>
        <id>https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/5-landing-page-builders.html</id>
            <category term="Uncategorized"/>

        <updated>2020-05-24T18:57:52+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Landing Pages - You can call it the lifeline to convert your&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Landing Pages - You can call it the lifeline to convert your target leads to potential customers. It's the key to Conversion.</p>
<p>A Digital Marketing Campaign is lifeless and unplanned without a Landing Page. Marketing is all about converting those targeted leads to lifelong potential customers. Without Landing page, your visitors might get confused about what to do next. Where to take the step? Where to see the details of what made them click on your ad?</p>
<p>Honestly, generic homepages can never serve your purpose of lead conversion. It needs a particular page that pinpoints all the specific consumer needs. That's how they will convert.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, a landing page doesn't build up on its own.</p>
<p>But, you don't need to run after the coders to design it from scratch.</p>
<p>Trust me, its pain.</p>
<p>So what to do?</p>
<p>The good thing is there are plenty of tools out there to make the whole process of creation &amp; management more comfortable for you, and you can create them in a fraction of time. A single landing page might not serve your purpose, for a successful campaign, you need to experiment with multiple designs and lead form placement within the landing page. So managing and optimizing your set of landing pages for better performance, it's pretty well become your full-time job until you have a single dashboard that helps you to optimize and manage effectively.</p>
<p>Landing page builders can save your precious time &amp; money as well.</p>
<p>{But before moving forward with the landing page builders, let's understand the difference between a landing page and a home page and why they are so important.</p>
<p>What is a Landing Page?}</p>
<p>As per updates in 2019, the market is full of excellent landing page builders. Here I am listing some for you which are catching the heart of all. Though each of these has its strengths and weakness, I will mention them all for you so that you can pick up the ultimate one to fulfill your business needs. Also, you can do better do A/B testing with the trial versions before picking the one.</p>
<h3>1. Elementor</h3>
<p>Starting with the best one which I have frequently been using.</p>
<p>Elementor is a WordPress plugin with the drag &amp; drop feature. It provides you a wholly original and separate interface for creating posts, custom post types pages. So when you open a standard format of creating posts or pages, you get a new button that allows you to enable the elementor, and then its a completely different and straightforward page editing process.</p>
<p>The best thing it can be done through a handy user interface, and you don't need to have any prior knowledge or skills about HTML or PHP. As it works on the frontend, it will show you the outcome right away so that you can visualize where it is going to stand. You can create any layout for your page regardless of what your current WordPress theme allows you to do. Also, it can quickly gel up with all the WordPress themes.</p>
<p>You can create impressive content structure and page layouts, even if you are not a designer or doesn't have site building coding skills. As per the latest report by elementor, they claim that their plugin has been downloaded for more than a million times.</p>
<p>If you are not willing to create a page from scratch, you can pick one from their pool of ready to use templates and tweak them a little to get your desired output.</p>
<h4>Pricing</h4>
<p>It's free. Hahahaha.</p>
<p>No, let's keep it real. Elementor offers an unlimited premium package, but honestly, you might not need it that much.  The main plugin is available in the official WordPress repository. <a href="https://wordpress.org/plugins/elementor/">Here</a> is the link. You can install the plugin and get started immediately. There are no hidden costs.</p>
<p>Now talking about the pro-edition, there are some extremely cool features for the power users, and you can customize your CSS, work on your form straight from elementor, add slides, integrate woo-commerce, more content, more template blocks, etc. But it is not something which everyone needs so pick for yourself wisely.</p>
<p>The current pricing chart of Elementor,</p>
<p><img class="wp-image-2567 aligncenter" src="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/media/posts/16/Screen-Shot-2019-09-29-at-8.34.59-AM.png" alt="elementor-pricing" width="800" height="600" /></p>
<h4>Pros &amp; Cons of Elementor</h4>
<ol>
<li> It have impressive features and is easy to use</li>
<li>It allows you to build custom pages</li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Best Webhosting for Mautic CRM</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/best-webhosting-for-mautic-crm.html"/>
        <id>https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/best-webhosting-for-mautic-crm.html</id>

        <updated>2020-05-24T18:57:53+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Top Web Hosting for self hosted Mautic installation | Best 5 Web&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <h1><strong>Top Web Hosting for self hosted Mautic installation | Best 5 Web hosts</strong></h1>
<p><strong><span style="color: rgb(153, 153, 153);">By Ankit Sharma</span></strong>, September<span style="color: rgb(153, 153, 153);">&nbsp;4, 2019 11:00 AM</span></p>
<p>Welcome to my comparison and review for the Top Web Hosting for Mautic. Well that you are here, I can tell you that you love the capability and the power of Mautic but you are not able to make optimum use of it due to either the lack of technical assistance and setup or due to the incompatibility of the Web hosting platform. <strong>I have been personally using Mautic for me and my clients for about 3 years</strong> now and have handled all the nitty gritty things about it. Web hosting is just one of them. I have listed my favourite web hosting solutions for hosting Mautic installation. These are the factors I used to review my best choices for Mautic hosting :</p>
<ul>
<li><strong><u>Loading Speed</u></strong> - Mautic is a heavy system and requires a fast optimised server to host it so as to avail good loading speed.</li>
<li><strong><u>Cron Jobs</u>&nbsp;</strong>- Not all web hosting will allow you to run the cron jobs the way you want them to run. Running cron jobs directly consume the server bandwidth and many web hostings (Specially shared one's doesn't allow them on complete autonomy )</li>
<li><strong><u>Support</u></strong> - As Every hosting environment is comprised of different technology and infrastructure. This might case few functionalities of Mautic not work for you. In such a scenario, hosting support must help you and resolve your issue.</li>
</ul>
<h2><a href="https://ankit.digital/recommends/kualo" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51);">Kualo Hosting</span></a></h2>
<p><span style="color: rgb(53, 52, 52);">Kualo is my favourite choice considering the quality of Support they provide and the Robust service they have. Best thing about Kualo is their <strong>60 Days money back guarantee.&nbsp;</strong>This comes only because they are confident about their service.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span style="color: rgb(53, 52, 52);">They will help with free migration of your mautic installation to their server.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p><span><a href="https://ankit.digital/recommends/kualo" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><img alt="" width="533" height="529" title="imgppp1"  src="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/media/posts/18/imgppp1.png"></a></span><br />
<h3>The Good Stuff:</h3>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-family: Roboto; font-weight: 300; font-size: 17px;"><strong><u>Full Account Isolation </u></strong>:&nbsp;</span>Accounts are isolated with a caged file system that prevents privelege escalation and information disclosure attacks.<span style="font-family: Roboto; font-weight: 300; font-size: 17px;"></span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 17px;"><span style="font-weight: 300;"><span style="font-family: Roboto;"><strong><u>No Noisy Neighbours</u></strong> :&nbsp;Each customer is allocated it's own resource pool, meaning other users can't cause downtime or slow performance for your website.</span></span></span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 17px;"><span style="font-weight: 300;"><span style="font-family: Roboto;">​<strong><u>Machine Learning Firewall </u></strong>: Multiple firewall layers featuring machine learning and collective intelligence keeps bots and hackers at bay.</span></span></span></li>
<li><span style="font-family: Roboto; font-weight: 300; font-size: 17px;"><strong><u>Malware Defense </u></strong>: We automatically patch vulnerabilities in a wide range of web applications and quarantine known malware, keeping your site and visitors safe.</span></li>
</ul>
<h3>The Bad Stuff:</h3>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-size: 17px;"><span style="font-weight: 300;"><span style="font-family: Roboto;">To be frank, I could not find any drawbacks about Kualo. And I have always find their services and support staff as awesome as always. So I don't have any point to mention here.</span></span></span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="color: rgb(53, 52, 52);">5/5 Stars</span></p>
<h2><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51);">A2 Hosting</span></h2>
<p><span style="color: rgb(53, 52, 52);">Security, affordability and support is what I love A2 hosting for. I have used it not just to host my Mautic installations, but my other web projects as well. They claim to have 20X fast servers when compared with others in the industry. They offer <strong>any time money back guarantee.</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="color: rgb(53, 52, 52);"><strong>​</strong></span></p>
<p><span><img alt="" width="533" height="529" title="imgppp 2"  src="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/media/posts/18/imgppp-2.png"></span><br />
<h3>The Good Stuff:</h3>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-family: Roboto; font-weight: 300; font-size: 17px;"><strong><u>20X Fast Servers</u></strong> : Their exclusive Turbo Server option offers you the fastest hosting experience!</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 17px;"><span style="font-weight: 300;"><span style="font-family: Roboto;"><strong><u>Guru Crew Support </u></strong>: Their friendly and knowledgeable support team is available 24/7/365 to help!.</span></span></span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 17px;"><span style="font-weight: 300;"><span style="font-family: Roboto;"><strong><u>Perpetual Security</u></strong> : An average of 30,000 sites are hacked each day globally. Their Perpetual Security measures <strong>help prevent you from becoming the next victim</strong>! That's why your account include&nbsp;<strong>free HackScan Protection</strong> to help block hacks before they can do damage to your site. </span></span></span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 17px;"><span style="font-weight: 300;"><span style="font-family: Roboto;">A mere 1-second page load delay impacts your bounce rate, SEO rankings and even your conversion rate. You won't have to worry about any of this when you choose A2 Hosting and our&nbsp;<strong>screaming fast SwiftServer platform</strong>!</span></span></span></li>
</ul>
<h3>The Bad Stuff:</h3>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-size: 17px;"><span style="font-weight: 300;"><span style="font-family: Roboto;">Their basic package is fine, but when you upgrade, it appears to be little costly in comparison to other web hosts.</span></span></span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 17px;"><span style="font-weight: 300;"><span style="font-family: Roboto;"></span></span></span><span style="font-size: 17px;"><span style="font-weight: 300;"><span style="font-family: Roboto;"></span></span></span>Although their support is friendly and cooperative but sometimes they charge for minute stuffs which other hosts can do free for you.</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="color: rgb(53, 52, 52);">4/5 Stars</span></p>
<h2><span style="color: rgb(51, 51, 51);"></span>SiteGround Hosting</h2>
<p>SiteGround is one of the most secured shared hosting provider. They are known for their super experienced and technically skilled support staff. I have been using them for my valuable and high end clients's project. You can trust them when it comes to speed and security.&nbsp;</p></p>
<p><span><img alt="" width="533" height="529" title="imgppp 2 copy"  src="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/media/posts/18/imgppp-2-copy.png"></span><br />
<h3>The Good Stuff:</h3>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-family: Roboto; font-weight: 300; font-size: 17px;"><strong><u>Technical Superiority </u></strong>: Developing smart in-house software solutions and adopting innovative new technology that make their clients’ sites faster.&nbsp;</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 17px;"><span style="font-weight: 300;"><span style="font-family: Roboto;"><strong><u>Wordpress Trusted </u></strong>: They are featured as the</span></span></span> hosting provider recommended by WordPress.org - the most popular, community-driven site building software worldwide. Even though it has nothing to do with Mautic, but getting recognition from an open source community means a lot.&nbsp;</li>
<li><strong><u>Security first Mindset </u></strong>:Their dedicated security experts proactively write custom patches and rules to our WAF that stop multiple identified-yet-unresolved third-party software vulnerabilities.</li>
</ul>
<h3>The Bad Stuff:</h3>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-size: 17px;"><span style="font-weight: 300;"><span style="font-family: Roboto;">Their shared hosting is one of the costly service in the industry. Though it comes with higher security in hand but are priced higher when compared to other good quality hosts. Their upgrades and higher end servers are even expensive.&nbsp;</span></span></span><span style="font-size: 17px;"><span style="font-weight: 300;"><span style="font-family: Roboto;">​</span></span></span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 17px;"><span style="font-weight: 300;"><span style="font-family: Roboto;">They might charge you extra which other hosts can do for free. Example - Migration of your websites from other hosts to their hosting.&nbsp;</span></span></span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="color: rgb(53, 52, 52);">3.5/5 Stars</span></p>
<h3>And the winner is...</h3>
<p>To be frank, there are really lesser number of Web hosting solutions that offer Mautic operating compatibility. Almost every web host provides <strong>Softaculous</strong> these days and that contains Mautic One Click installation service. But this doesn't necessarily mean that those Web hostings will let you operate Mautic installation in peace. Mautic in itself is a heavy tech infra demanding software which needs high quality server requirements that does not only host your Mautic installation with fast servers but also let you run all the important cron jobs.&nbsp;</p></p>
<p>I find <strong>Kualo</strong> as one of the highest reliable, cost friendly and support backed solution as a Mautic host. It has solved all the shortcomings mentioned above for me and I believe it should do the same for you.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em><span style="color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"><strong>WINNER</strong></span></em></p>
<p><span style="width: 100%;"><img alt="" width="1200" height="627" title="company-rating"  src="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/media/posts/18/company-rating.png" style="width: 100%;"></span>
<p>You can easily take their services hassle free. They offer 60 days money back guarantee which in itself is a sign of confidence. You can ask for refund anytime in 6o days if you aren't satisfied for whatsoever reason.&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong><span style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">NOTE : I have reviewed here only 3 Web hosts as I find them reliable after using them. All the other hosts not mentioned here are either crapy or doesn't provide good services. All these 3 have their own pros and cons and I do not mean to demean any of them. You can choose any of these web host at your discretion.</span></strong></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">© 2019, Ankit.Digital . All rights Reserved | <a href="https://ankit.digital/privacy-policy/"><span style="color: rgb(250, 37, 20);"><u>Privacy Policy</u></span></a> | <a href="https://ankit.digital/disclaimer/"><span style="color: rgb(250, 37, 20);"><u>Disclaimer</u></span></a></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Disclaimer</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/disclaimer.html"/>
        <id>https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/disclaimer.html</id>

        <updated>2020-05-24T18:57:53+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Disclaimer for https://ankit.digital If you are using this website, you agree to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Disclaimer for https://ankit.digital</p>
<p>If you are using this website, you agree to the terms and conditions of using this website. This disclaimer is for educational purposes for all of our visitors. We review products and services in the website. We post educational information in this website. At times use some brands logos and their brand names for the educational and promotional purposes, in all such cases, the copy rights and trademarks belong to the actual product or service owners and not to this website. Some reviews published on this website may include external links to the products. If you happen to purchase with those links, it may lead to an affiliate commission to us. At all times, we recommends users to use this website and buy products from internet at their sole discretion only.</p>
<p>If you would want to get in touch with us, shoot an email at ankit[@]editsoftdigital[dot]in</p>
<p>Thanks.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Privacy Policy</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/privacy-policy.html"/>
        <id>https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/privacy-policy.html</id>

        <updated>2020-05-24T18:57:53+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Your privacy is important to us. It is Editsoft Digital Pvt Ltd's&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Your privacy is important to us. It is Editsoft Digital Pvt Ltd's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, <a href="https://ankit.digital/">https://ankit.digital</a>, and other sites we own and operate.</p>
<p>We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.</p>
<p>We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.</p>
<p>We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.</p>
<p>Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.</p>
<p>You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.</p>
<p>Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.</p>
<p>This policy is effective as of 4 October 2019.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Let Facebook Chatbot handle your Sales and Marketing | Messenger Marketing Automation</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/let-facebook-chatbot-handle-your-sales-and-marketing-or-messenger-marketing-automation.html"/>
        <id>https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/let-facebook-chatbot-handle-your-sales-and-marketing-or-messenger-marketing-automation.html</id>

        <updated>2020-05-24T18:57:52+05:30</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to promote Nutraceutical products with Digital Marketing</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/how-to-promote-nutraceutical-products-with-digital-marketing.html"/>
        <id>https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/how-to-promote-nutraceutical-products-with-digital-marketing.html</id>
            <category term="Strategy"/>
            <category term="Digital Marketing"/>

        <updated>2020-05-24T18:57:53+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/media/posts/24/ankit.digital.jpg" alt="" />
                    There are various uncovered aspects of selling nutra products online. And I&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/media/posts/24/ankit.digital.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>There are various uncovered aspects of selling nutra products online. And I will uncover them all in this blog post. When it comes to promoting nutra products it is important to choose your promotion methods accurately and these methods are valid even if you are a seller or if you are the manufacturer. This blog post will also cover digital marketing for nutracuitical products and company.</p>
<p>I would be very precise and calculative in explaining my process based approach. Sales in ecom industry is a function of good process. So we have to implement all the digital marketing strategies in order to complement good process that can ultimately build unlimited sales funnel. Let's begin step by step.</p>
<h2>Digital Strategy to Sell Nutraceutical products with digital marketing</h2>
<ol>
<li>Building an online E Com Store is very important if you want to have good sales without being dependent on third party platforms like Amazon, Flipkart and others. We recommend building this store using Shopify due to the responsive features of shopify and having it's adaptability in scaling the store as much as we wish to. <strong>We are shopify partners in India and so we can also help in store building part</strong>, if not developed already.</li>
<li>Influencers Outreach. To have better marketing of our products via social media and other mediums, we need to reach out to influencers and experts in the industry and collaborate with them to promote our products. These influencers can be - <strong>Health Experts | Health Bloggers | Food Bloggers | Gym Trainers | Nutritionist | Fitness Freaks and many more</strong>.</li>
<li>Influencer outreach program can be further categorised in two models - <strong>Pay Per Post</strong> and <strong>Become an Affiliate.</strong></li>
<li><strong>Launch Giveaway : </strong>To increase the organic reach for our products, we can introduce weekly giveaway of our products. These giveaway's shall have certain rules that will directly impact the virality of our products. You can have a look at one of the good case study of Kingsumo. <a href="https://sumo.com/stories/viral-giveaways" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://sumo.com/stories/viral-giveaways</a> . We use Kingsumo to create viral giveaway's .</li>
<li>Promote and Run ads around multiple lead magnets. There are various lead magnets including - Ebook | Health Guide | Checklist | How to PDF's and so on. Let me put an example here. Here's an E Book on "<strong>Nutrition as a part of Therapy in the treatment of Liver Disease</strong>" . Now this Ebook will have useful content for the patient that shall include our products. Also, we run ads around this lead magnet to promote it and then build our sustainable email list. Two benefits we got - We sent out our product promotion to the prospect in terms of e book and we also have the prospect's email address.</li>
<li>These lead magnets can be promoted FB, Insta, Google, Native Ads, Pinterest, Youtube Videos. This promotion can be organic and paid.</li>
<li><strong>Launch Drip campaigns around email lists</strong> build from lead magnets. For example. In the above case, lead magnet was the ebook for Liver patients. So we have prospects to whom we can always followup regarding our products related to Liver. Or we can ask them to schedule a free appointment with our Nutritionist for better understanding on improving liver problems. Such drip campaigns focuses on sending series of emails on various parameters. These parameters can be Last email open or not, E Book downloaded or not, visited our landing page or not, Abandoned cart or not. Below  drip chart is an example of drip email series. We use our in-house built app called <strong><a href="http://sell3x.com">Sell3x</a></strong> to perform email marketing automation.  Here's an example of a drip email campaign. <img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2549" src="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/media/posts/24/WhatsApp-Image-2019-07-02-at-11.57.05-PM.jpeg" alt="" width="771" height="658" /></li>
<li>Let us say we have got 1000 email subscribers from our lead magnet - <strong>Nutrition as a part of Therapy in the treatment of Liver Disease. </strong>Now we send out email campaigns as a drip series. Each email shall contain a link back to our landing page or store. This will have two impact - <strong>Sales or No sales</strong> from our E Com Store. If it's a sale, very good. If it's not a sale, we will put all this audience who clicked on the link and visited on our landing page on Facebook and Google re-marketing ad funnel. This ad funnel shall show ads to audience claiming 25% flat off on their first purchase.</li>
<li><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Email Marketing</strong> </span>- Email marketing needs to be done for various process.- Asking Gym Trainers, Celebrities, Influencers, Food Bloggers, Nutritionist and others to join our Affiliate program and our outreach program.- Reaching out our prospects through email lists.- Emailing existing customers to buy again.The entire strategy will not be focused on just one marketing channel. We will leave no DM channel unturned and employ all the strategies in parallel so as to have aggressive promotion and sales in the process.<strong>Concluding Notes</strong> -  Digital Sales is a function of a optimised digital marketing process. And we at Editsoft Digital are highly inclined towards building the same process.</li>
<li><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>Remarketing Campaigns</strong></span> - There's a saying in internet marketing that it takes 7 attempts for a visitor to convert into a customer. This means that you have to get into the eyes of a prospect atleast 7 times so that he could make a decision. Re-marketing comes in here. We do this with the help of Facebook and Google Ads. If some one has visited your website once, you can make him visit your landing page / website / lead magnet or anything related by re-marketing him.</li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>While I was preparing these strategies, I prepared some notes and on the basis of those notes, I was able to describe the strategy above. Although, there are few things that might bring more clarity when you see those notes. Have a look below.</p>
<p>[gallery ids="2551,2552,2553,2554"]</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Digital marketing is all about how creative you can be. And when it comes to be innovative about your approach, I am cent percent sure about how my team would execute the plan perfectly. So, in the end it matters about the execution only. There are a lot of places available over internet to find about new plans, ideas and promotional methods but the thing that owns the result is just the execution. Thus, my suggestion to have full focus on the implementation part and then take your project ahead.</p>
<p>In any case, you feel like I becoming your digital partner or consultant in helping you take your business to a greater height, just let me know here - Contact Me</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Long Tail Pro Review</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ankit Sharma</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/long-tail-pro-review.html"/>
        <id>https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/long-tail-pro-review.html</id>
            <category term="SEO"/>
            <category term="Reviews"/>
            <category term="Internet Marketing"/>

        <updated>2020-05-24T18:57:53+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/media/posts/23/Long-Tail-Pro-Review.png" alt="" />
                    If you are searching for the best keyword research tool to grow&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://ankituproi.github.io/ankit.digital/media/posts/23/Long-Tail-Pro-Review.png" alt="" />
                <p>If you are searching for the best keyword research tool to grow your business online then I assume that you already know the basic of how to do keyword research and importance of doing keyword research. Searching for the best list of keywords which have low competition and high amount of searches isn't difficult if you have chosen the right tool to find the keywords.</p>
<p>So today we will be investigating about this tool: Long Tail Pro keyword research tool. How effective is it to find the best suitable keyword for your niche? What's different in it? How effective is it to automate your keyword Research? We will also do the comparison between LongTail Pro and other specialized keyword research tool in terms of their features and functionality.</p>
<p>But first, let me tell you more about me. And why I am making bold statements about Long Tail Pro Review.</p>
<p>I am in the blogging field from 3 years now and have learned everything by experimenting on my blogs. I have used many keyword research tool in the first year of my blogging journey and became constant with Long Tail Pro from 2 years now and will continue to do so. Keyword Research is the beginning, if you are doing SEO of your article and targeting the right keyword can be a game changing for your blog. So keywords must be chosen wisely.</p>
<h2>Long Tail Pro Review</h2>
<p>Before going deep in the investigation of Long Tail Pro first we need to know what is Long Tail Pro</p>
<h2>What is LongTail Pro?</h2>
<p>Long Tail Pro is compelling keyword research tool which assists the user to choose a Longtail Keyword. It generates a list of thousands of possible long tail keywords within minutes from a single root keyword or multiple root keyword. It started as an adobe air based application and now it is available as a cloud-based application online.</p>
<p>It fetches the data from google keyword tool to pull all the keyword data related to a specific set of keywords that user wishing to analyse. With a root keyword, you can generate a huge list of all the relevant keywords along with their monthly search volume, Cost Per Click, competition level with advertiser &amp; Long tail keywords. The metrics for long tail keywords is only available for platinum users.</p>
<p>So Long Tail pro allows generating a huge list of all possible long tail keywords from a single root keyword or multiple seed keyword, quickly, effectively and efficiently. With this list of keywords, you can analyse the each on the basis of their search volume, CPC, competition level and select a small list of keywords that are good to include in your content or Pay Per Click Campaign.</p>
<p><strong>Unique Feature:</strong> The keyword competition metric of Long Tail Pro is a unique and best feature which decide the difficulty level of the keyword.</p>
<h3><strong>How keyword competition metric calculated? </strong></h3>
<p>So let's go in deep of how and on what basis it analyse the keywords. Long Tail Pro inspect the first 10 display searches of the root keyword and applying its calculations with the metrics like Page Link, Domain Authority, Page Rank, Site Age, Moz rank, Juicing Page, URL, and Title. After calculation, it displays the competitiveness of the keyword ranging from 0-100. The keyword at the first position is the easiest to rank while the one at the last is the highly competitive keyword.</p>
<p><strong>Good competition score: </strong>If you have a new website, it's good to target keywords with competition score less than 25 and up to 40 for the already established site.</p>
<h3>Is it the only tool with Keyword competition Metric?</h3>
<p>So as I have mentioned earlier that the unique feature of Long tail Pro is Keyword Competition Metrics but Long tail pro is not the only keyword research tool who has it's own competition metrics. Moz had developed its own competition metrics which is named as "keyword difficulty". It's a percentage based metrics as it measures the competitiveness of the keyword in %, the higher the percentage - the more it is difficult to rank for.</p>
<p>If we compare both the tools Moz and Long Tail pro on basis of keyword competition metrics, as per my experience I'd say Long Tail Pro is much more reliable as the comparison to Moz. However, we can't review the keyword research tool on the basis of competition metrics only. To give an objective review I will dig deeper into the usability of this tool.</p>
<p>So Long tail pro can be categorised in 3 core categories:</p>
<ol>
<li>Keyword Research</li>
<li>Rank Checker</li>
<li>Competitor analysis</li>
</ol>
<h2>Long Tail Pro Keyword Research Feature:</h2>
<p>As we have already discussed a glimpse of how this keyword research feature of Long tail pro works. You just need to add one or more seed keyword and click on generate results. It will showcase all the possible long tail keywords related to the seed keyword. But there is much more than this in Long tail Pro. They are other different advanced features that you can use, such as importing a list of seed keywords from an external source. Also, you can filter the results on basis of no. of words in a query, cost per click &amp; no. of searches.</p>
<p>Once you have clicked the generate button, Long Tail Pro usually takes 1-3 minutes to load the result with the list of keywords. The result loading speed depends upon the type of the seed keyword you have entered and the scale of the result list. After the resulting load up, it displays a nicely laid out version of Google Keyword Planner. The difference between two is that you need a monthly subscription of Long tail Pro to calculate competitive metrics of each keyword.</p>
<p>To conclude this feature of Long Tail Pro: a nicely laid sorted design with the ability to delete irrelevant keywords and add relevant keywords to your favourite tab, these feature a similar to that of google keyword planner. So here I don't see any huge advantage of spending $$$ on Long Tail pro monthly subscription.</p>
<p>However, Long Tail pro offers a unique feature as 'keyword competitor' metric and this is the biggest advantage of using long tail pro but as it is not available for all the users of Long Tail Pro. I will rate this feature 5 out of 10.</p>
<p><strong>Personal rating: 5/10 </strong></p>
<h2>Long Tail Pro Competitor Analysis Feature:</h2>
<p>Competitor analysis of long tail pro is for sure a better feature to count on. It allows you to analyse the first ten results on google with that individual keyword. LTP calculates the competitiveness of the keyword by analysing the results on the basis of  9 data points:</p>
<ul>
<li>PA ( Page Authority)</li>
<li>PL ( Page Links)</li>
<li>DA ( Domain Authority )</li>
<li>Moz Rank</li>
<li>Site Age</li>
<li>PR ( Page Rank )</li>
<li>Juicing Page</li>
<li>URL</li>
<li>Title</li>
</ul>
<p>Above data points are very important and useful in considering the competitiveness of the keyword. Long Tail Pro uses these feature to analyse and the results are laid out in a table structure which is easy to understand by a user.</p>
<p>Considering only this feature isn't unique as there are many others keyword research tools offering the same. But, if you have purchased the monthly subscription you can gain the benefits of keyword competition metric for the keyword you are analysing.</p>
<p>For this tool to be of any significant the competitor analysis tool must have keyword competition metric. Without the keyword competition metrics, the competitor analysis metrics is not simply useful enough. Though its time saving but keyword competition metrics makes it much easier.</p>
<p><strong>Personal Rating: 6/10</strong></p>
<p>Now let's discuss the last feature of Long Tail Pro which is the Rank Checker. For the people who have the understanding of Search engine Optimisation (SEO) must be familiar with this term. Having a tool which can check the ranking's on the website with a targeted keyword and that too on daily basis is pivotal. Well, Long Tail will take care of this feature.</p>
<h2>Long Tail Pro Rank Checker Feature:</h2>
<p>If you guys are familiar with rank checking tools or used one before. You must be clear that there are several other rank checking tools available in the market. So what makes Long Tail pro special in this feature? The rank checking feature of long tail pro is inbuilt which makes it handy to use.</p>
<p>You can simply add the keyword and the domain URL and set the country you wish to target. Click on check rank to see the results. Long Tail Pro will compile the results on the basis of your preferences and you will see the position number on google, yahoo and bing.</p>
<p>So basically it's a very simple feature and is an important and useful one. So simple addition of this feature in long tail pro is a good offering. It obviously good to have one tool which provides you with the features of many other marketing tools.</p>
<p><strong>Personal rating: 8/10 </strong></p>
<p>So far we have discussed the 3 core categories or I should better say core features of Long tail Pro. I have mentioned all that I have examined with my experience and I hope my personal ratings to these features will be help for you to understand the Long Tail pro features. So what mostly we have discussed is the good part of Long Tail Pro. But I would like to share some of the issues I faced while using a Long tail pro to make the picture clear of how it is.</p>
<h2>Long Tail Pro Issues:</h2>
<p>Well! I might go blunt here sharing my experience. I have been using Long Tail pro from two years now and I haven't seen any update that actually had any changes to its functionality or interface. Also, the biggest problem I experience is it's the inability to consistently bring back the data. And this happens to me frequently and I haven't found any solution to this problem.</p>
<p>Though I had a back to back email conversation with the long tail pro team but still I face the similar issue. When I create a new campaign and try to use the pre-establishes dataset with the new seed keyword, the keyword analysis feature pop up with a load box but nothing happens, it just keeps on loading.</p>
<p>This is the biggest problem I face in using Long Tail Pro and to be very honest, this is really frustrating for me sometimes. To be honest, there is no other problem there in using Long Tail pro. Though there are some features which can be added to Long Tail pro but I won't be discussing them here.</p>
<p>Well! there are many things in life which aren't perfect actually nobody and nothing is perfect. But for sure Long Tail Pro is the best tool for doing keyword research</p>
<p>So far I have discussed the main features of Long tail pro and the issues I have experienced. Now I will discuss who is the intended user of Long Til pro and I will tell you if its a go for you or the bad in giving it a chance.</p>
<h2>Who should purchase the Long Tail Pro?</h2>
<p>If you have an established website and searching for the content keywords ideas to drive more traffic to your website then definitely you can give a try to long tail pro as it will provide you with the keywords to work on and rank the website on those keywords.</p>
<p>If you don't have a website but still murmuring the idea and planning to create one. Why don't you try entering some seed keywords and see what it give you.</p>
<p>If you are not sure where to start with, think about the topics that interest you and the things that you are passionate about, products and news you recently interacted with. Collect some seed keywords from them and click go. Might be you get the right idea to work on.</p>
<p>In case you are an advertiser, Long tail pro can really be helpful for you to collect all the dataset of the keywords together so that you can put a bid on the right keywords.</p>
<p>So basically if you are spending a significant amount for doing keyword research using Google Keyword Planner, or if you haven't started using one. I will suggest you go with Long Tail Pro.</p>
<h2><strong>Pricing : </strong></h2>
<p>Long Tail Pro offers plans for 3 categories:</p>
<ol>
<li>Starter Plan: In this, you can search for 10,000 keywords per month.<br />
Monthly subscription is of $37 per month<br />
Yearly subscription will cost cheaper as $25 per month</li>
<li> Pro Plan:  With this, you can search for 25,000 keywords per month<br />
Monthly subscription is of $67 per month<br />
Yearly subscription will cost cheaper as $45 per month</li>
<li> Agency Plan: With this, you can search up to 60,000 keywords per month<br />
Monthly subscription is of $147 per month<br />
Yearly subscription will cost cheaper as $98 per month</li>
</ol>
<p>The trial version of all 3 plans costs only <strong>$1 for 7 days.</strong> I will suggest you opt for trial version first, as it is cheap and you can yourself judge how effective it is.</p>
<p>After dicussing alot about Long Tail pro and its features, Here I am summing up all its pro's and con's to make you learn about it.</p>
<h2>Pros and Con's of Long Tail Pro:</h2>
<p>Long Tail Pro was rated as the best keyword research tool by the industry experts and is used by more than 1 Lac digital marketers all around the world. It's very effective in finding the low competitive keyword in the most competitive niches. Also providing a detailed report of SEO metrics to analyze and filter the keywords to use. But just like any other thing it also have its flaws. So let's have a look at the pro's and con's of using Long Tail Pro</p>
<p><strong>Pro's </strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Real-time filtration: It filters keywords and show results by no. of words, cost per click, local searches, keyword competitiveness and the level of advertiser competition.</li>
<li>Calculate keyword profitability: It uses the Rank Value feature to determine the keyword profitability</li>
<li>10x faster than desktop version: The Long Tail pro cloud is much faster than the adobe air desktop version.</li>
<li>Keyword Competitiveness Metrics: As described earlier, this is the best feature of Long tail Pro.</li>
<li>Custom Targets: Long Tail Pro tool calculates keywords competitiveness you should target on the basis of your own domain metrics.</li>
<li>Majestic SEO data Integration</li>
<li>Exports Results: You can export the list of keywords, metrics data, google top 10 results etc.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Con's </strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Still needs more minutes to calculate in bulk for an extra large set of keywords.</li>
<li>The Rank Value metrics it shows isn't definite.</li>
<li>It cannot easily segment results for individual root keywords.</li>
<li>There are few noticeable bugs in the cloud version in comparison to the desktop version.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Reviews by Industry experts:</h2>
<blockquote>
<p style="text-align: center;">"I’m a fan of Long Tail Pro! It’s a powerful keyword research tool that I’ve used and am very impressed. I definitely recommend Long Tail Pro. It’s a must-have tool for any SEO or Internet Marketer."<br />
Pat Flynn – SmartPassiveIncome.com</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 style="text-align: left;">Alternatives to Long Tail Pro:</h2>
<p>As I mentioned the prices earlier, the trial version of Long Tail Pro is cheap enough to give it a try and I think you should. In the trial period, your can test and judge the tool yourself.</p>
<p>Moving forward towards the alternatives, there are several other keyword research tool in the market and almost each of them comes with a trial version. So you can give a try to them as there is no tool which does everything.</p>
<ol>
<li><strong>Moz </strong><br />
Moz offers a 30 days trial version after filling the credit card. Though it reminds you few days before the tril completes.<br />
Moz actually doesn't work as a keyword research tool but you can pair it up with Long Tail pro or Google Keyword planner to find the competitiveness of the keyword, analyzing the top results and the competition websites. And doing this you can finally track down rankings of targeted keywords.</li>
<li><strong>SEM Rush<br />
</strong>Sem rush offers a 14days trial. The pro version is of $69.5 per month and then there is a guru and business plan which are very costly.<br />
Its a great tool for keyword analysis and competitor analysis but similar to Moz it doesn't provide the list of additional keywords related to your seed keyword.</li>
<li><strong>Authority metrics<br />
</strong>This one is new in the keyword research tool market and is very similar to Long Tail pro. Created by some guys from No hat digital Authority Metrics is definitely worth looking at. They offer 30 days money back guarantee, so you have plenty of time to review this keyword research tool.</li>
<li><strong>Google Keyword Planner<br />
</strong>Duuhh!! List can be completed without google keyword planner. It is alpha &amp; omega of keyword research tools. and its free to use But you must have an Adwords account to login in the Google keyword planner. It will show you results like the Average Monthly Searches, competition level of the keyword(Med, High, Low), and the cost per click (bid) on the targeted keyword. But there is a small problem. A recent change in keyword planner range the monthly searches in 7 volume sizes  0–10, 10–100, 100–1000, 1000–10000, 10000–100k, 100k–1MM and 1MM+. So we can see the huge swings in the min-max search volume and the accurate searches are available for only those who are high paying ad buyers.</li>
</ol>
<p>Though I am recommending the alternatives but I am not using any of them. Sound silly to me.</p>
<p>Well I am using long Tail Pro, ahrefs, SEMRush and sometimes I also use Google Keyword Planner. Actually, I use them all together, combine their results to analyze the Search Engine Page Result to understand the overall market place.</p>
<p>So I think it's time to wrap it up. I would conclude by saying that I really enjoy using Long tail pro and I am a big fan of its keyword competition metric. It had helped me to filter the thousands of useless keyword and still doing them same today. I think its the most affordable keyword research tool available in the markets with great features like keyword competition metrics, so I will recommend using Long tail pro.</p>
<p>Though I will not recommend it purchasing without the Keyword competition metrics as I don't find it simply amazing without keyword competition metric and it wouldn't benefit you much.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote>
<p style="text-align: center;">Keyword Research is the Blueprint of a succesful Search Engine Optimized Startegy.<br />
Make your choices wisely.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
